So how did your test go?
I feel pretty good about it,
but I won't know for a few days.
Well, we're all pulling for you.
We are?
You cannot kick me while I'm doing my job.
I thought you could give me an answer to my question about you...
moving in.
I have a dog.
That's not a dog.
It's a hyena, escaped from the zoo dressed in dog clothing.
I love dogs.
as doctors,
we are trained to be skeptical
because our patients lie to us all the time.
The rule is,
every patient's a liar until proven honest.
Why aren't you prepping for rounds
- and stealing all the good cases?
- Well,
why aren't you prepping for rounds
and stealing all the good cases?
No reason.
Lying is bad...
or so we're told,
constantly, from birth.
Honesty is the best policy.
The truth shall set you free.
I chopped down the cherry tree.
Whatever.
I'm waiting for mcdreamy.
I'm avoiding burke.
Why are you avoiding burke?
he thinks I moved in with him.
Why are you waiting for--
mcdreamy's doing me a favor.
Burke "thinks"you moved in with him?
Wait, you're calling him "mcdreamy" again?
The fact is,
lying is a necessity.
thank you for doing this,
with the needles and the blood.
They won't accept her without a full family history.
I'm happy to get your mom into the clinical trial,
even with the needles and blood.
All done.
How's that feel?
We lie to ourselves because the truth...
the truth freaking hurts.
It feels good.
Burke "thinks" you moved in with him.
What does that mean?
Okay, it's not important.
You're calling derek "mcdreamy" again.
It's nothing.
All right,what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Stop repeating what I say.
Stop asking me questions.
cujo has to go!
He peed on my bed.
My bed, meredith.
- He's our dog.
- No, he's not my dog.
You two bought him without even asking me.
We rescued him from certain death.
Come on, you guys.
I'm putting my foot down.
Either the dog moves out,or I do.
Foot down now.
Me or the dog,
which is it?
You hesitated.
She hesitated!
You hesitated?
I didn't hesitate.
I was thinking.
You have to think about it?
Fine.
I'm moving out right now.
Later, I'm moving out later because right now,
I have rounds.
Tell me that is not a dog.
it's not a dog.
rick freeark, he's 29.
Severed 3 fingers on his left hand.
Controlled the bleeding in the field.
Vitals stable.
Gave him 5 of morphine on the way in.
The fingers?
I had some trouble retrieving them,
so we took off.
Rig behind us found 'em.
They're iced and ready to go.
- Ten minutes out.
- Great.
Continue with I.V. Fluids and start a course of antibiotics.
- Yang, you wait outside for the fingers.
- Yes!
You can sew 'em back on, right?
'Cause they sewed that guy's penis back on after his wife chopped it off, right?
Penises and fingers are like apples and oranges.
How did it happen?
I was loading my gear onto the truck for a gig,
and they got caught in the lift gate.
You're a musician?
I play the freakin' guitar.
You can sew 'em back on, right?
This is not that big of a deal, right?
Oh, dude, I better not be out of the band.
Captioning provided by touchstone television and abc, inc.
Captioned by closed captioning services, inc.
---------------------------------
www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents
Sync:YTET-Wangyq0680
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
Greys Anatomy
Season 02 Episode 15
---------------------------------
well, the cuts look clean.
That's good.
A clean sever makes reattachment easier.
Now I'm not gonna lie to you,
if the surgery is successful,
we're looking at a long recovery with lots of physical therapy.
Do you smoke?
Why?
Cigarette smoke constricts the blood vessels.
I've seen really good grafts fail over a few cigarettes.
So what are you saying,
I-I smoke a cigarette after my operation,
and--and, boom,
my fingers fall off?
No, first they turn black and necrotic,
and then they fall off.
Well... I don't smoke,so...
really?
'Cause judging by the nicotine stains,
your fingers do.
anybody out there?
Hello
don't look at me.
She had hip replacement surgery a month ago and was discharged last week.
Then why is she still here?
Because I am not a bouncer and this is not a nightclub.
I am doing what I can with extremely limited staff and resources,
and if you have a problem with that,
take it up with the chief.
don't know why there's no sun up in the sky stormy weather...
mrs. Larson's got to go.
If she refuses to leave,
what can I do?
She's 78 and nonambulatory.
You have the upper hand here.Use it.
Oh, karev, can I talk to you for a second?
The results of your medical board exams.
Wh--aren't you gonna open it?
Yeah, I'll open it.
I'm weary all the time
oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, mrs. Larson,I'm dr. O'malley.
Oh, an irishman.
I love the irish.
They have a--
a sparkle.
You can see it in the eye and the swagger.
Come on, dr. O'malley,
show me the swagger.
The eyes are right,
but, uh,
you'll have to work on the swagger.
Mrs. Larson...
call me sophie.
Now be a doll and bring me a remote.
This one's busted.
Sophie...
I can't bring you a new remote
because you're no longer a patient at this hospital.
Now according to your chart,
you have a room waiting for you at the sugar maple nursing home.
I'm staying until my daughter's house is ready.
She's converting her den into my bedroom.
She's doing it in a shade of pink.
Now... bring me a remote, irish.
I'm going to sing until you get back.
- Can't go on everything I have is gone stormy weather
- coming right up.
yumi miyazaki, uh, 22,
presented this morning with persistent hiccups.
She was given 50 chlorpromazine,
which stopped them for awhile,
but then the hiccups returned,
so she needs a surgical consult to rule out esophageal perforation.
When did your hiccups start?
A few days ago.
She doesn't speak english.
Are you her boyfriend?
Her coach.
Oh, she's an athlete.
Oh, yumi's a competitive eater.
Eating is a sport?
Uh, miyazaki.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's like a rock star in japan.
Again, eating is a sport?
Tell her I saw her on tv.
Tell her I'm an athlete, too.
I'm a wrestler.
she wonders how a wrestler got smart enough to be a doctor.
Most wrestlers she knows are dumb.
just tell her
she hasn't been hanging out at the right gyms.
How about instead you tell her that
a persistent hiccup could be an indication of something much more serious.
schedule an esophagram.
Oh, she is competing this afternoon at the taste of seattle.
Can't you just give her a stronger dose of that drug?
It seemed to work.
Did the hiccups come back?
- Yes.
- Then it didn't work.
Ohh.
- Dr. Bailey?
- Be quiet.
dr. Bailey,are you okay?
all right, somebody page addison shepherd.
there he is.
Heartbeat's strong.
Since there's no dilation or effacement,
looks like nothing more than braxton hicks.
Except?
I know the mild-concern tone.
I've used myself from time to time.
Sometimes, false labor is the body's way of telling you to slow down.
I'm a surgeon.
I understand the realities of your job,
but you need to understand the realities of your pregnancy
and take it easy.
If there's anything I can do to help--
well, yeah, for starters,
you can help me get up off this table.
Dr. Bailey...
the G.I. Lab has a couple of questions about ms. Miyazaki's esophagram.
All right, let's go.
dr. Stevens.
Keep an eye on her today.
Watch out for any painful contractions,
more than five in an hour,
anything that could indicate preterm labor.
The favor's not for me, stevens.
You know that.
naomi cline, 43,
had her tricuspid valve replaced three years ago with a porcine valve, sir.
Well, naomi,
I'm surprised to see you back again so soon.
Pig valve usually holds up 10 to 15 years,
but yours seems to be degenerating a little too quickly for my comfort.
Oh, heart valve,
schmeart valve.
I got married,dr. Burke!
I found him--
my true love, my...
you jump, I jump.
look...isn't it beautiful?
And look--
look at that beautiful,
beautiful man.
we, uh,
met in the grocery store.
Oh, honey.
Congratulations.
It's good to see you so happy, naomi.
Yeah.
Uh, so naomi's heart valve...
wh-what does this mean?
Oh, there's an underlying cause for your wife's valve failure that remains undiagnosed.
Theories, grey?
Rheumatic fever,
chronic use of migraine meds...
or I.V. Narcotics could all cause, uh,
valve disease, sir.
Oh, I don't use drugs.
Don't need 'em.
I've got tom.
He's my drug.
aren't you, baby?
She's high, dr. Burke.
No, she's in love.
She's happy.
Nobody is that happy.
She's on drugs.
Run a tox screen,
but naomi doesn't strike me as a liar.
If she says no drugs,
then there's no drugs.
You develop a sixth sense about these things.
Everybody's a liar.
dr. Grey, is that a dog?
No.
Keep this elevated for awhile, okay?
I'm gonna check in on you in a little bit.
Hey, yang.
You were a little harsh in there.
Well, he was lying.
Besides, your harsh is another man's refreshing.
Well, he's in shock.
You know, he lost his fingers and his only remaining habit all in one day.
We need to be compassionate.
Compassionate?
Yes, it's an emotion.
Have you ever heard of it?
Well, have you?
She's barely back on her feet,
and you've got her calling you mcdreamy again.
Now I was just telling the patient the truth,
so you might want to try it sometime.
Remotes...
- remotes.
- O'malley.
I'm--I'm getting a remote for mrs. Larson.
What happened to the upper hand?
Have you met mrs. Larson, sir?
Why do you think she's been here this long,
in a private room?
She handled you, too?
Well, she sang for the troops, you know?
Can't we just keep her here
until her room at her daughter's house is ready?
No, we can'T.
Not on surgical service,anyway.
Oh. Okay.
But some other service?
I'm the chief, o'malley.
I can't condone turfing patients onto other services.
You hear me, o'malley?
I'm, uh, I'm missing my program, irish.
And I don't see a remote in that hot little hand.
I noticed your urine output has increased slightly since yesterday.
I'm gonna have to take you to gynecology to make sure you don't have a prolapsed uterus.
Honey, my uterus hasn't been an issue for 30 years.
I know, but it might be an issue now.
You know, one that could keep you here in the hospital for tests.
You drive.
I'll ride shotgun.
You're not moving out,george.
Oh, yes, I am.
I gave an ultimatum.
I threw down the gauntlet.
I drew my line in the sand.
Well, un-give,
un-throw, un-draw.
A man does not give an ultimatum and then back down.
Meredith had a choice,
and she chose the dog.
A girl chose a dog over you?
- Yes.
- No.
- Are we gonna do this or what?
- Yeah, let's--
let's go.
Don't start without me.
We're not gonna start if izzie doesn't focus.
- Izzie, come on.
- What should I put on the flyer?
- I don't--
- destructive, aggressive hell dog available?
- That's not helping.
- Fine.
Uh, playful, protective puppy.
Need loving home.
Good.
I know.
- Hey, george.
- Don't talk to me!
You'll only make me mad.
You're gonna mess up my game and I'm in the zone.
Okay.
What are you doing?
- Oh, it's a flyer.
- izzie
- I'm gonna put it up--
- izzie, come on.
Okay.
Keep your panties on.
All right.
No touching!
go!
You're advertising for a home for doc?
I said I would do it?
And you haven't,and you won'T.
And I don't want george to leave.
Well, at least put that he's not housebroken.
what? It's the truth.
- Okay, so you want me to put the truth.
- Fine.
Vicious, hyper devil mutt is available
and will pee on your bed.
He's your dog, too.
We got him together.
We got him together,
but he's not my dog.
He's not your dog, either.
He doesn't even know us.
We are not home enough for him to know us.
it's a record.
It's a record!
she's cheating.
I beat your asses.
you wanna be me,
but you can't be me
but you...
crap, she's gonna blow.
- run!
- Aah!
"the surgical floor
"has become a dumping ground
"for patients who aren't even surgical.
"We are overworked and exhausted.
- "This makes for--"
- the nurses again?
Can't you do something about this?
You used to be one of 'em.
Don't you speak nurse?
That's why you don't get any respect from the nurses--
surgical arrogance.
I'm not arrogant.
You're killing 'em with that workload.
Look at the board.
What?
That's a beautiful board.
It's a crowded board.
We need more nurses.
Mr. Kamaji,this is probably what's causing her hiccups.
A tear in the lining of her esophagus.
Can you fix it?
Yes, surgically,
and the sooner the better.
After the competition today,
her schedule is clear until march.
No, her schedule is clear now.
She can't compete today.
And if she enjoys the taste of solid food,
I recommend giving up the sport for something a little less aggressive,
say boxing.
I see.
Could you give us some privacy, please?
Karev...
get the translator up here.
Let's make sure she's gettin' the whole truth.
Put that out.
Sorry.
I've gotta prep you for surgery.
Can you ask your friends to leave?
I wasn't gonna light 'em.
I was just holding 'em.
Okay.
Seriously, take 'em.
Throw 'em out.
No, you hang on to 'em.
Seriously, I wasn't gonna smoke.
Seriously, I don't care.
Do what you want.
You don't think I'm gonna be able to quit, do you?
No, I don'T.
- I'm lonely all the time
- oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Irish.
That nice lady doctor in gynecology said that
since I had a hysterectomy back in '74,
I don't have a uterus to prolapse.
Damn it.
I've been feeling a bit feverish.
A woman my age with a fever could be an indication of,
oh, any number of awful diseases.
They took your temperature an hour ago.
It was normal.
I am sorry, sophie,
but I am gonna have to call your daughter.
I'm telling you, I'm warm.
That must be one hell of a dog.
Excuse me?
With those eyes...
and those nice,
firm hands...
a girl chooses a dog over you...
it must be one hell of a dog.
Mrs. Cline's tox screen
and titer both came back negative.
I was sure I was right about that.
Gonna have to adjust your worldview, dr. Grey.
There are people out there who don't lie.
Maybe.
Although, frankly,
the drug use would've explained the valve failure.
So how do we proceed?
Let's schedule mrs. Cline for her surgery.
Okay.
Do you want to come over for dinner?
- What?
- Dinner--
our place--
mine and cristina'S.
Why?
You're cristina's best friend.
I want her to feel welcome to have her friends in our home.
Oh, so she moved in with you?
Yes.
Didn't she tell you?
Of course she told me.
Why wouldn't she tell me?
She's in, right?
Which, you know,
I think is great.
Great.
Thank you.
Just came from mr. Freeark's room.
He's convinced he won't be able to quit smoking.
Says you agree.
Well, he asked my opinion.
You want me to apologize?
No, I want you to go in there and tell him that you're wrong,
that you're having a bad day,
that your favorite uncle died of lung cancer
and every time you see a cigarette, you freak out.
Say whatever you need to say,
but get him to believe that this is about you,not him.
Because if he thinks he won't be able to quit, he won'T.
Then we shouldn't even do the surgery.
Fine.
What is your problem?
I'm your boss.
- What is the matter with you?
- Shut up.
You're not my boss right now.
We're in an elevator.
That's your specialty, right,
mcdreamy moments in elevators?
Dr. Yang.
For a moment, I'm not dr. Yang
and you're not dr. Shepherd.
You're the guy who screwed up my friend,
the guy who drove her to get a dog
she can't keep a dog she only got
- because her boyfriend lied to her about his wife.
- I never lied to her.
I know a liar when I see one
'cause I'm a liar.
Fine, you want me to lie to the patient?
Fine, I'll lie.
Yumi.
Hey, the translator's here.
Where's the patient--
miyazaki?
She left with her friend about 20 minutes ago.
She wasn't discharged.
Sorry, we're short staffed.
I assumed someone else had done the paperwork.
Damn it.
Unh! Come on!
What are you doing out of bed?
I gotta get a candy bar, man.
You're on morphine,
you're about to have surgery and you can't eat.
Mr. Freeark, please.
- My dad's mr. Freeark.
- Careful.
He's got a combover
and an--an annoying wife named kimberly, so--
rick, listen,
earlier, I was out of line.
No, it--
you got me to think.
I don't want to be a guy sittin' in a bar with a stump for a hand,
having a smoke ten years down the line,
bragging about how I used to play better than dave navarro.
Yeah, you don't want to be creepy, bitter guy.
Here's the thing...
my last cigarette was this morning.
Only I-I didn't know it was my last cigarette.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
He's making me stand at the back of the O.R.
While he reattaches rick's fingers.
I mean, I can't even touch a retractor.
I hate him.
Truth--
did you move in with burke or not?
I told him I moved in with him,
and I'm keeping my old apartment.
What?
I sleep at burke's every night,
my clothes are there.
So I still have my apartment.
Big deal.
You have to tell him.
Actually, I don'T.
So...
I'm supposed to go to dinner at your fake apartment with the guy you fake live with?
Oh, I would never have you over to dinner with burke.
That's weird.
This is my point.
Stop with the lying.
And you're being honest?
The last time you called him mcdreamy,
you were all atwitter with love.
- We're just friends.
- Uh-huh.
We are.
West nile virus,
are you kidding me?
No, look at her.
She's feverish.
She's much weaker than she was this morning.
She could be decompensating.
she's been here for a month, dr. O'malley.
Have you see any mosquitoes in this hospital lately?
Oh, such a handsome young man.
Those chocolaty eyes.
In order to test you,mrs. Larson,
we have to do a spinal tap.
Will you be doing it?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, then...
- call me sophie.
- You got it.
Nice meeting you, irish.
So, if you'll just sign here,
- we can go ahead and schedule you for surgery.
- Okay.
You know, you are a gorgeous young woman.
Look at you.
You should smile more.
Mr. Cline.
Oh, uh...
do me a favor.
Sure.
Don't tell her you saw me.
I'm not sure that I'm going to go in.
She'S...
she can be exhausting.
Yeah, she'S...
really happy.
Y-you know, I thought it was just,
you know, falling in love,the wedding.
But I was kinda hoping the honeymoon would be over by now, you know?
I mean, it's not normal,right?
nobody's that happy.
Run a tox screen on naomi cline.
Oh whose orders?
Dr. Burke's, of course.
I'm sorry to bother you.
The paramedics are on their way in with yumi miyazaki.
She collapsed at the taste of seattle and is vomiting blood.
Damn fool.
Probably tore her esophagus in two by now.
All right.
Mm.
Are you okay?
complications of boerhaave's syndrome.Go.
Pleural effusion,
sepsis, shock.
She's cyanotic with shallow breath sounds.
B.P. 76 over 42.
Tachycardic to the 130s.
Started her on high-flow 02
and her second bolus of saline.
all right,let's get her to the O.R.
they're ready and waiting.
Her freakin' coach should be the one on this gurney.
Let's keep our eyes on the prize, karev,
saving this woman's life.
I'll meet you guys up there.
Me, too.
Hey, hey.
What are you gonna do, punch him out?
Yeah.
So you're gonna kick his ass,
get yourself kicked out of the program
before you have to open your board scores just in case you failed.
god, you're such an idiot.
Dr. Karev, how do I begin the esophagomyotomy?
Cut proximal and distal to the tear to expose the mucosal defect.
Correct.
Then we'll move to debridement of the defect--
ohh!
Dr. Bailey,that's preterm labor.
That's not a braxton hicks contraction.
You're in labor.
Why didn't you call me sooner?
All right,let's get out of here.
I was gonna fashion a gastric patch.
I taught you the procedure.
Now leave.
here. Get that clamp.
I got paged, dr. Grey.
Jeffrey wanted to give me the results of the extensive blood work that I ordered.
You forged my signature?
That's really bad, right?
Yeah, that's really bad.
Naomi is not on drugs.
The tests came back negative.
They did?
They did, again.
Next time you forge my signature, let me know.
Save me a trip.
That's it?
You're not gonna yell and say, "damn it, grey,"
and storm out?
I will if you want me to.
No.
Dr. Burke,
here's another one.
Her serotonin level,
it's through the roof.
Dr. Grey, you took a detailed history.
Mm-hmm.
When did mrs. Cline develop asthma?
After the first surgery.
Why?
We found a carcinoid tumor in the lung.
Very rare,
almost impossible to diagnose.
It masks itself as a bunch of seemingly unrelated symptoms--
adult-onset asthma,
valve failure...
an increased level of serotonin in the blood...
which creates a false sense of euphoria.
So naomi's not actually this happy?
She just has a tumor?
exactly.
Thank god.
You people with your tumors.
I tell you,I'm infected with love.
I'm sorry.
Your body is lying to your mind.
Oh, let the lie continue.
Right, baby?
Uh...
how soon can you cure her?
Tomorrow we can take the tumor out.
If all goes well,
naomi goes back to normal.
Great. Thank you, both.
Thank you for not chewing me out for forging your signature.
Thank you.
I know it was probably you who convinced cristina.
She's very strong,
but she listens to you.
If you told her to move in...
anyway... thank you.
No problem.
Now do you have any sensation in your left arm at all?
No.
- Actually, could I watch?
- yeah.
It's okay.
I want to see every blood vessel and nerve
I'm gonna screw up if I ever smoke again.
Not that I'm gonna...
ever again.
I smoked my last cigarette.
Okay.
Let's get started.
The nursing home says she never showed up.
How exactly is that possible?
She wouldn't leave.
My mother is old and infirm.
You couldn't make her leave?
Have you met your mother?
Fine.
Where is she now?
Oh, hi. I'm dr. O'malley.
She's in the infectious disease service.
Infectious disease?
Since when does she have an infectious disease?
She doesn'T.
She just doesn't want to leave.
She's unbelievable.
Yeah, she is.
So is her room ready?
'Cause I can go get her right now.
They have had the room ready for weeks.
No, uh, not at, uh,
sugar maple.
I meant at your house.
I'm sorry?
The--the pink room...
at your house.
hi, sophie.
Irish.
What a wonderful surprise.
You won't catch my disease, will you?
No, I think I'll be okay.
sophie, uh, your daughter was just here.
Uh... nursing homes...
are for old people.
I know I'm elderly.
I do know that.
But if I have to go to that place...
I'm afraid...
I'll become old.
I don't think that's possible.
Oh.
You know that I--
I would keep you here if I could?
Oh, no, darling.
You can't waste any more time with me.
You have to go ball's out with the dog.
Excuse me?
So she chose an animal over you.
So what?
Oh, women are fools.
That's old news.
But life's too short for you to give in, irish.
So fight.
You fight for what's yours.
Now that, my friend...
is a swagger.
I'll be closing the peritoneal cavity with zero chromic sutures.
Thank you.
Chief?
Let's get back to it.
Pull back on that retractor.
Give me more suction.
I'll need a sponge on a stick.
What's going on?
I tried,but you wouldn't listen.
It is now 6:07.
The second shift nurses start at 6:00.
They're not coming in.
Do you have any idea what a sick-out would do to this hospital?
I've already put in the call for temps.
What's this?
Official notification.
We go on strike in ten days.
You're doing good, yumi.
You're doin' just fine.
we should get the translator back up here.
She doesn't understand what's going on.
We'll be back.
What the hell are you doing here?
I never would have...
I thought she would be fine.
I'm sorry.
Don't tell me,tell her.
Tell her how her career is over because of you.
Way better than punching him out.
Hey, uh...
can you...
you want me to open it?
Yeah, you know, it'S...
I can't, so...
I-I shouldn'T.I mean, I--
look, you already think I'm idiot.
It won't be any great shock.
Congratulations.
You are not an idiot.
Except when you're...
being an idiot.
Hey, how's he doing?
Uh, jonesing for a cigarette,
but I think he'll make it to the end of the day.
Good.
I was being nice to her.
Okay.
I can be nice without being,you know...
mcdreamy. I know.
I really can.
Okay.
Okay, then.
Bed rest at home until the baby comes.
You do know what bed rest is,
don't you, miranda?
Yeah, hell.
Hell with tv and books.
Here, it's from all of us.
I may be 47 months pregnant,
I may be on bed rest,
I may not be able to see my own feet,
but I am dr. Bailey.
I hear everything,
I know everything.
I'm watching each and every one of you.
And I will return.
strike?
Strike.
You are all a bunch of arrogant surgeons.
- Hey.
That was izzie.
She refuses to take the dog home.
Mm-hmm.
Fine, if you want me to tell burke I didn't move in,
I'll tell him.
No. Don'T.
What?
Don't tell him.
At least, not right now.
Or tonight.
I just mean wait.
It can wait.
I lied about derek.
We're not just friends.
I mean, I'm not.
He's still mcdreamy.
I know.
You don't get to choose.
I know you've been going through a bad time,
I know you miss shepherd,
and I know that your life has been admittedly pretty unpleasant these days.
You get points for breathing in and out,
you get to be a little selfish,
but you don't get to choose a dog over me.
I'm george.
I sleep down the hall from you.
I buy your tampons.
I have...
held your hand every time you've asked.
I have earned the right to be seen...
to be respected,
to not have you think of me as less than a dog that you got at the pound.
So...
I'm not moving out.
Whether you like it or not,I'm staying.
No matter how hard we try to ignore it or deny it...
eventually,
the lies fall away...
I'm glad you moved in.
So am I.
Whether we like or not.
Okay, doc...
let's go.
hey, doc.
Hey, buddy.
Welcome home. Well...
How are you? Yeah.
He's beautiful.
We brought his toys.
Oh, here's his food and his water dish.
Oh, okay. Hi.Here.
Thanks for doing this.
Uh, I know it's a lot to ask.
Oh, it's all right.
It's just a dog.
Right? Come on, doc.
uh...
we'll just wait--
- wait in the car.
- Okay.
So, he, uh... chews everything.
So don't leave anything out.
he hates cats and small,
little yappy dogs.
- Oh... not housebroken.
- Oh.
I probably should've told you that.
Yeah.
you don't have to do this, you know?
What? I--you know,I got all this land.
It's just goin' to waste.
Derek.
It's just a dog.It doesn't mean anything.
He'll be fine.
Yeah.
Okay.
- Good night.
But here's the truth about the truth--
it hurts.
So we lie.
Sync: YTET-Wangyq0680
-==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
www.tvsubtitles.net