Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
That was amazing.
Meredith won't be an issue.
She's out of my life.
Goodbye, Derek.
Think about moving in with me.
She likes you.
Don't let the syph get in the way.
I like you, Olivia.
I just don't like you enough.
Do you feel like doing it now?
You're married?
I'm pregnant, you blind moron.
- How much sodium did you give?
- 500 cc's over 4 hours.
Why didn't you follow up?
I gave you one thing to do.
I have a lot to teach
if you want to learn.
So when you decide how important
it is for you to hate me, let me know.
Dorie Russell, giving birth to quints.
We're gonna need
all the hands we can get.
40 years ago The Beatles
asked the world a simple question.
They wanted to know
where all the lonely people came from.
My latest theory is that a great many of
the lonely people come from hospitals.
More precisely,
the surgical wing of hospitals.
I have the best quint.
Lucy. She just smiled at me.
- She's nine hours old, George.
- I'm saying.
There are five babies here and
clearly mine is the advanced one.
Charlotte's smart.
She's got wrinkles on her forehead.
Very serious.
OK, A: this is not a competition,
and B:
my quint kicks your quints' asses.
Emily's strong,
she won't let go of my finger.
Hey, Julie has her organs
on the outside of her body
and she's still alive, thank you.
Kate's the best one.
- Izzie.
- Leave.
Can we please just talk?
You're too busy screwing nurses to talk.
Just get out.
Can someone make sure
- that Kate's vitals remain stable?
- I will.
He is unbelievable.
I am so glad I never slept with him,
which is his loss,
because I'm really good in bed.
Mind-blowing.
Mind-blowingly good in bed.
Are you trying to seduce us?
And then he sleeps with Olivia
instead of me. Olivia.
- Hey, I slept with Olivia.
- Well, then you both have bad taste.
You can't say that you weren't warned.
Alex has always been Alex.
You dodged a bullet, Iz.
You're better off without him.
Why are you even surprised?
You sleep with a snake, you get bit.
Thanks, guys... for the support.
- Who's on call tonight?
- I am.
All right.
The rest of you, go home, sleep.
All five quints are still alive.
It's a good day.
As surgeons we ignore our own needs
so we can meet our patients' needs.
We ignore our friends and families
so we can save
other people's friends and families.
Which means that at the end of the day,
all we really have is ourselves.
And nothing in this world
can make you feel more alone than that.
I made breakfast.
I don't have time for breakfast.
I've gotta round
before everyone else does
if I wanna get the good cases.
You know that.
Right.
Well... coffee?
Bye.
So I was thinking, we...
I mean, me and you, could maybe
go to Joe's later
to talk by ourselves...
- Why should I move?
- You live on a campground.
It's 40 acres of
the most beautiful land in Seattle.
I didn't give up a Central Park
brownstone to live in the forest.
Our house in the Hamptons had trees.
- They were The Hamptons.
- Why are you pointing?
- I'm sorry. What were you saying?
- Oh, nothing.
- Anybody have any food?
- You should eat breakfast.
God, you sound like Burke.
You know, sometimes I think
we'd be better off with dogs.
Preaching to the choir. I'm over men.
Real nice.
You know, a dog is not
a replacement for a human being.
You better wake her.
If Bailey catches her, she's dead.
Izzie.
- Izzie.
- Damn it.
What?
Hell hath no fury like a girl whose
non-boyfriend screws a nurse.
Bitch.
I like you bitter and pissed off.
You're almost like a normal person now.
OK, what do we got?
Karl Murphy, 52.
Multiple skin melanomas.
Underwent surgery to his nose, ear, and
a skin graft to the left index finger.
- How's the capillary refill?
- Slow, about four seconds.
What do you recommend
to get that blood moving again?
At this stage, our best option's
probably a biotherapeutic agent.
What... What is that?
- We put leeches on your face.
- Leeches? You don't say?
They secrete blood thinners that break
up pooled blood so it can be evacuated.
It's sort of like a big drain.
- If this makes you uncomfortable...
- No, no.
I've been a hiker for 40 years,
almost 40 years, yeah.
Mother Nature hasn't come up
with anything yet I haven't loved.
You a big outdoorsman?
How do you think I got all these
melanomas in the first place?
Oh, Dr. Shepherd. You're in early.
- If you'd like us to come back...
- No. Go ahead.
Robert Martin, 45, collapsed and hit
his head, causing a small hemorrhage.
That was the problem.
Mr. Martin was found to have
a Rathke's Cleft cyst on his pituitary,
and surgery was postponed when...
- When I told a nurse...
- Olivia.
When I told a nurse to administer an
incorrect dosage of hypertonic saline.
Dehydrating his brain.
He still has a chance.
He could wake up and be fine.
- There's a chance.
- I know I screwed up.
- Just put me back on this case, please.
- There's not much of a case left.
You saw to that.
You want back on? Be my guest.
Oh, good. Here you are.
Mom and Dad are anxious for an update.
Dr. Yang?
We've done the initial surgery
on Julie's omphalocele.
A primary closure was attempted
but there was pulmonary compromise
- so we couldn't continue...
- Yang, do this in plain English.
Oh, we operated
on Julie's external sac of organs.
We pushed in
as much of the bowel as we could
and we think we can push in the rest
with a second operation.
- She has to have a second operation?
- Yeah.
- Uh... Well, not for a few days.
- Dr. O'Malley?
We put in Lucy's brain shunt yesterday
and she's doing very well.
We have to keep monitoring to make sure
the spinal fluid doesn't back up.
- Stevens?
- Dr. Burke used a catheter
to open Emily's atrial septum
last night.
Today, we'll try to reconstruct
the left chamber of her heart.
- We're very hopeful.
- Dr. Grey?
Charlotte's lungs were
less developed than the others',
so we put a special mask on her
to help her breathe
and we're monitoring her closely.
- That just leaves Kate.
- She seems to be pretty healthy.
No major issues identified,
but we'll keep her in the Isolette
until she reaches four pounds.
You hear that, honey?
Kate's doing really well.
I'll be in my room.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Tom, she's just had five babies.
Her hormones are all over the place.
Give her time. She'll come around.
Grey, watch the mother. Make sure
her hormones don't get the best of her.
- I can look out for Dorie.
- No, you have Emily's heart surgery.
- But I have a relationship with Dorie.
- Why are you arguing?
- Why am I being pushed off...
- Hey, Stevens.
I don't know what you're angry about,
but I don't care. Keep it to yourself.
On top of every other patient under
our care, we have quints to worry about.
These are preemies. They should have
spent another eight weeks in the womb.
Like interns...
...they're not ready for the real world.
Oh, it's the pit. Yang, come with me.
Constance Ferguson, 40, inmate at
Henderson, swallowed a razor blade.
- Attempted suicide?
- Attempted field trip. Worked too.
All right.
- Field trip?
- Says on her chart she was in solitary.
- This is her way out.
- Oh, is she crazy?
Only if you'd call a murderer crazy.
Yeah, baby,
that's what I'm talking about!
Ms. Ferguson,
are you experiencing any discomfort?
You mean apart from these snazzy
handcuffs you got pinching my wrists?
Did you at least put tape on the blade?
- I'm not an idiot.
- You swallowed a razor blade.
- Not going to tell me what hurts?
- And shorten my vacation?
You're standing around. Why not
get me some chocolate pudding?
Make the blade go down smoother.
Get an X-ray. Portable. With prisoners
we have to minimize flight risk.
I'm supposed to check on Julie. You said
we're to keep a close eye on the quints.
Julie's my quint too.
I got that covered. You do this.
- Are you sure you can't do it?
- I can. I choose not to.
Come on, baby,
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I only murdered three people
and none of them were doctors.
- Olivia.
- Dr. O'Malley.
- How are the leeches doing?
- They're not. Can't get them to bite.
With all this blood?
Should be a no-brainer for a leech.
They can get anxious.
Bright lights, thunderstorms...
Oh!
- Nervous handlers.
- I'm sorry. I should be better at this.
I still get a little squeamish
around leeches.
That is not what I have heard.
Dr. O'Malley can take over from here.
Whoa, whoa. What was that all about?
Nothing.
Dr. Frank to Oncology.
OK.
There we are. He's in.
I had no idea that
you and Alex were a couple.
It's just...
I was having a bad day
and it was good to have someone...
To talk to, I mean, not good to...
Alex really is good.
I mean, he's good in the way
he's a good person, good.
Not the other kind of good.
You know, "good in bed" good.
Which he is, as I'm sure you know.
But...
OK. Well, bye.
- Any temperature spikes?
- No fever. Vitals are stable.
Very good.
- Go ahead, after you.
- Thanks.
- So, you're giving up the trailer?
- I'm not giving up the trailer.
Is Addison telling people
that I'm giving it up?
It's just funny. I just would never
have pegged you for that guy.
What guy?
You know, the marbled bath,
private pool, gated community guy.
- Don't peg me. I'm not peggable.
- You're pegged. Deal with it.
- BP's low. She's tachycardic.
- SATS?
Dropping on high-flow O2.
- No breathing sounds.
- Her lung collapsed.
- Should I call Addison?
- No time.
Stick this between her second
and third rib. Do not go too deep.
You're going to hear
a small gush of air.
I heard it.
- Nice job.
- Thank you.
- I'm not giving up the trailer.
- Whatever you say, Dr Shepherd.
- Her lung collapsed?
- And I know it sounds scary,
but it's really not that uncommon
in a preemie this size.
So, we've inserted a tube
into Charlotte's chest
and that will help her breathe
until her lung can stay up on its own.
Mrs. Russell...
She really is doing fine now.
That's me. I gotta go.
My mom can only handle the triplets
for half a day. She's 74 so...
- I'll call you when I get home, OK?
- Hmm.
I love you.
- Could you...
- I'll keep an eye on her.
- Thank you.
- OK.
Dr. Prunella to ICU, stat.
Dorie... this isn't your fault.
You can't blame yourself for this.
I've got one baby who can barely breathe
and one with half a heart.
Two of the others are...
If I'd listened to the doctors
I could have had three healthy girls
instead of four
who might not live until tomorrow.
It was my decision.
Tom agreed with the doctors.
So, really, Dr. Grey...
who else should I blame?
First step in the Norwood
is cardiopulmonary bypass.
With HLHS, what else do you get
besides hypoplasia of the ventricle?
Stenosis or atresia
of the mitral and aortic valves.
Why use the RV-PA conduit instead of
the modified Blalock-Taussig shunt?
- It limits diastolic runoff.
- Well, you've done your homework.
I was on call last night.
I study when I'm on call.
Well, no matter what the books say,
I guarantee you
you've never seen a heart this small.
Bet you I have.
How you doing, you?
You know, I'm having a baby too.
Yes, I am. A little boy.
Maybe you can meet him someday.
How's that sound?
Does that sound good?
We could...
Pregnancy has not made me soft.
I haven't gone soft. I don't do soft.
Of course not.
You were just talking to a patient.
- What's this?
- The inmate's X-rays.
That foolish, foolish woman.
She swallowed four razor blades?
Mm-hm.
Hey! Hey, you! Hey, Nurse!
- Would you keep it down, please?
- I'm starving.
You're NPO. No food allowed.
Come on, April, baby, don't go for him.
He's such an idiot.
I didn't come here to starve to death.
I want mint-chocolate-chip ice cream.
Mint, OK? Not Rocky Road. You better
not get me that Rocky Road. It sucks.
Thank God. Mama Bear,
help me out here, OK? I'm starving.
Don't give her anything.
Right there you're in official violation
of the Eighth Amendment.
You can't eat because
you're about to undergo major surgery.
What? What's she talking about?
You're at risk
for a perforated intestine
and half a dozen kinds of infection.
We need to operate right away.
I don't need an operation. I taped up
the blade. It passes the next day.
- What's the big deal?
- You swallowed four blades.
That's the big deal.
I thought it would buy me an extra day.
Does this operation
have a nice long recovery time?
You realize this is major surgery?
It's dangerous and you could die.
Mint chocolate chip.
I want at least a gallon after you
ghouls are done splitting me open.
What exactly is it that we're doing?
We're visiting.
We've thrown
all this medical talk at you
and outlined worst-case scenarios, which
has probably scared you half to death.
The one thing we haven't done is given
you a chance to be with your daughters.
Well, how is that going to help?
If I've learned anything, these past few
days, it's that I need to face reality.
Here's Kate. You can reach in
and touch her if you like.
I would like to very much.
Charlotte's not breathing.
Page Addison. She's in the OR.
We didn't see this on the echo.
You can never get an exact measurement.
What?
The baby's aorta
is narrower than we thought.
Diameter is only a millimeter.
- Just not getting enough blood flow.
- Damn.
I wanted you to see,
before I close up.
You didn't do anything.
- Dr. Stevens.
- We barely started.
Dr. Burke has done all he can for now,
so unless you know how to do a Norwood,
he's gonna close this baby's chest.
- You OK?
- I'm fine. May I go?
Yes.
- What happened?
- She had an apneic episode.
She's still not breathing on her own.
Intubate and give surfactant.
Push 0.1 of atropine
and three milligrams of ketamine.
- Meds are in.
- Tube.
OK. Place the CO2 detector.
- She was fine with the chest tube.
- That's the thing with RDS cases.
Just when you think the baby's
getting better, they slip right back.
Breath sounds equal. Good.
Mrs. Russell.
Unbelievable.
Who would do this to themselves?
The woman wasn't just in prison, Yang,
she was in solitary.
Well, she was seriously deranged.
You try spending a month locked
in a room with no windows,
no one to talk to for 23 hours a day.
See how deranged she is then.
- Dr. Bailey, she's a murderer.
- I didn't say she wasn't.
One, two, three.
I said, try having no one to make your
snarky comments to for a solid month.
My guess is
you'd swallow the entire razor.
- How are they treating you, Mr Murphy?
- I've done worse for company.
Oh, they're definitely filling up.
Tissue is getting nice and pink.
Make up with that
cute little girlfriend of yours yet?
Olivia's hardly my girlfriend.
- Is she OK?
- She?
Yeah, Isabella.
This one here on my finger...
that's Darcy.
And that little guy on my nose,
named O'Malley.
That's right, I named him after you.
You're the one that got him to bite.
Isabella is fine. She's just full.
Oh. Wait,
what are you going to with her?
She's done her job. We don't have
any more use for her.
- Except as medical waste.
- No.
I'd like to keep her... if I could.
Crazy nature man. You want to take a
leech home as a pet? That's fine.
You had no right
to speak to me that way.
Yeah? Well, you hurt my friend.
I had no idea Alex was seeing Izzie.
That's not what you're upset about.
You have no idea why I'm upset.
Besides, you know what
I don't understand is, why Alex?
And why again?
People get Ionely, George.
Hi, Mr. Russell?
It's Meredith Grey calling.
I was wondering if there was any chance
maybe you could bring
your boys by to visit their mom?
I think she could use the company.
Oh, the flu?
No, definitely don't bring them.
Thank you. You too.
You've been lying low.
Well, nobody's talking to me
so it makes it kind of easy, right?
I'm talking to you.
In short monosyllabic sentences
laced with disdain and contempt.
So, what, according to girl rules,
now you all have to hate me?
I don't hate you. If my mother hadn't
gotten Alzheimer's, I'd probably be you.
- Oh, really?
- Really.
Before she got sick, I mean, I...
I'd finished college,
but I was partying way too much,
staying out way too late to keep a job.
At family reunions everybody
was embarrassed to talk about me.
So that's what you think of me?
Are you OK?
- I almost killed a guy yesterday.
- Mr. Martin?
I'm trying to find
anything I can to help.
OK, well, what are we looking for?
Uh, anything on central
pontine myelinolysis.
- Unbelievable.
- Izzie.
- Izzie, come on.
- "Come on?"
You're fraternizing with the enemy
and you tell me to "come on?"
- Alex and I are sort of friends.
- Since when?
Since when are you and Alex friends?
You tell me to cut my losses,
and as soon as I turn my back...
- You're making too big a deal of this.
- Right. Of course.
I'm the unreasonable one. Do what
you want. Sleep with him for all I care.
Obviously I'm not going
to sleep with him.
Why not?
You've slept with everyone else.
Your surgery went smoothly. You'll
have abdominal pain for a day or two...
- Just a day or two?
- We'll watch until your bowels move.
- The average is about 36 hours.
- 36?
Four razor blades
and that's all you can give me?
Come on, sugarplum,
I thought we were having fun.
- Don't leave.
- What?
Just maybe a little conversation?
They've got me here by myself. I thought
I'd have a room mate to talk to.
OK.
Why did you kill three people?
Start off with a little small talk,
why don't you?
I was high.
On meth.
And I had this boyfriend who...
had this robbery all planned out.
He said that he would leave me
if I didn't help him.
Things got out of control.
He was gonna leave me.
He was all I had.
I would have been all alone.
Clearly, being alone has its benefits.
You paged me?
A leech fell off
and I can't get the new one to bite.
I'm sorry, they freak me out.
- I'm a surgeon, Olivia.
- You're an intern, George.
You know what time it is?
Time for you two kids to kiss
and make up, that's what time it is.
Mr. Murphy, we are not a couple.
Oh, you can't pull much over on me.
I say there's something
between the two of you.
You're right, Mr. Murphy, there was.
Olivia, this isn't the time
and this really isn't the place.
He broke up with me for a girl
who doesn't know he's alive.
- She does know.
- You, Meredith Grey?
Never gonna happen.
- Why would you think it's Meredith?
- Anyone paying attention
knows how you feel about her.
Except Meredith,
which should tell you something.
Sorry, Mr. Murphy.
She gave me syphilis.
Remember what you did to me
when I was an intern?
How could I forget?
You didn't speak to me
for almost a year.
But you learned.
Yeah, well, I think I gotta do that
to Izzie Stevens.
Well, she's smart, hard-working. Gets
a little too involved with her patients.
- A lot like you.
- I know.
It took me a long time to recover.
But it made you a better surgeon,
Addison.
The question is, is she talented enough
to make the lesson worth it?
She's the best I've seen in years.
I was hoping that we could...
You're not here to make friends.
You're here to make better surgeons.
And being the teacher
can be a Ionely business.
I'm telling you,
Meredith was all over him.
Seriously? She was all over him?
Mounting him? With the babies watching?
She would have been
if I hadn't interrupted.
- She was talking to him.
- You don't talk to bastards who cheat.
- You weren't his girlfriend.
- Not the point.
It is. I don't get emotional
over people I'm not dating.
Really?
You want to go there?
- No.
- I am having a moment here.
Don't mess with me.
You're not gonna have
a nervous breakdown or kill yourself?
No.
So... there's no chance you'll kill us?
- Oh, that was wrong on so many levels.
- So good.
- That was... That was good.
- It was good. It was good.
Your lungs are not good.
I know we got you out of there a little
earlier than you would have wanted.
We have to find something to help you.
So, if you have any ideas, Charlotte...
- Dr. Stevens.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Something you need?
- Yes, Dr. Burke and I have reassessed.
There's a chance with the Norwood
if Emily can make it through
the next ten hours.
- Would you look after her tonight?
- I was on call last night.
- But, I mean, yeah, of course.
- Good.
I've left a list of meds, and you're
familiar with pediatric life support?
Got certified
soon as I got in the program.
OK, then.
Anything else I should know
to look out for?
No. That should do it.
- Should I notify Mrs. Russell...
- No. I've done that.
Dr. Stevens,
this baby is your responsibility.
- She better be alive when I get back.
- OK.
I found studies where they
used aggressive plasmapheresis.
- This could work on Mr. Martin.
- Those were all isolated cases.
The studies
resulted in improved symptoms.
No trials have been done.
There is nothing you can do.
- What about thyrotropin?
- No.
- There's European studies...
- Karev, it's over. You screwed up.
You fried Mr. Martin's brain.
He wakes up; you put him in
a wheelchair. He dies; you killed him.
Deal with it.
Dr. Stevens, the baby's VO2
is still 40 per cent after transfusion.
- How's her BP doing?
- Still low. Last systolic was 52.
OK, I'm going to push
30cc's of NS manually.
Nice start. Pressure's 65.
- Hey, Iz.
- OK, really?
You think I'm talking to you?
Well, I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
When Derek broke up with you, I never
said "You're better off without him."
It's not supportive, it's condescending.
I was there. All I ever am is there for
you guys, and the one time I need you...
Just... go away, Meredith.
She was fine
then she just started seizing.
She's not seizing, she's choking.
Oh, my God. She swallowed a light bulb.
- We're losing her.
- Don't you think I can see that?
She needs an airway.
She's clamped down. I can't intubate.
We need some help in here!
- Want me to get paralytics?
- No, she'll be dead by then.
I need a scalpel for a crich.
- Have you done one ever?
- Of course not! Go!
I was gonna do a crich.
- How long has she been unconscious?
- She just went down.
Prep OR Two. Emergency thoracotomy.
Cristina, it'll be OK. Come on.
- She's coding.
- Again?
OK, uh...
Turn up... Turn up the epi drip.
OK.
- Hey, Dorie. What are you doing?
- I'm packing.
You've just had major abdominal surgery.
- You're not in any condition...
- I'm going home.
I need to go home. I can't be here.
I can't watch them die.
They're not dying.
They're trying to live.
You leaving them
isn't going to help them.
- I have boys who need me.
- Your daughters need you.
Don't you understand that I can't do it?
I can't do it.
- They're too sick.
- Which is why they need their mother.
- If Emily dies I...
- If Emily dies it will be horrible.
But if Emily dies and you're not here?
- I can't even hold them.
- But you can sit with them
and talk to them.
And let them know they're not alone
in this world. That's all they need.
That's all anybody...
- What?
- I think I know how to help Charlotte.
I don't know why
I didn't think of this sooner.
- What are you doing?
- Co-bedding.
Hospitals sometimes do it with twins
when one of them is sick.
- And the other one gets better?
- It helps.
- How?
- We don't really know.
Sometimes babies get stressed
in the ICUs from all the activity.
This way there's someone there
to comfort them.
To be there with them.
Excellent blood flow at all three
places. You're healing nicely.
- And I like my new nose.
- Your wife will like it, too.
I'm not so sure what she'll say
about your new houseguests.
I'm going to let these guys go in the
lake near my favorite hiking trail.
They saved my face. The least I can
do for 'em. And I don't have a wife.
- I'm sorry. Your wedding ring...
- I'm divorced. Just never took it off.
By the way... sorry you had
to see that little scene earlier.
Talking with the girl
who isn't your girlfriend
about the girl
you'd like to be your girlfriend?
Yeah.
She shouldn't have said that stuff.
It was just...
She was very unprofessional.
Yeah, but is it true?
Do you like this Meredith?
I don't think that's really
any of your business.
She's OK.
I like her OK.
All right. I love her.
Oh, come on. Don't be embarrassed.
I loved my wife.
But sometimes, no matter how much
you love someone,
they just can't love you back
in the same way.
Believe me, son, livin' with a woman
who can't love you back?
Way Ionelier than bein' alone.
What do you wanna do?
- We can... we can put her on ECMO.
- Baby this size,
you're risking intracranial hemorrhage.
She's already coded three times.
You page Dr. Shepherd?
She said you have to handle this.
- What? I'm an intern. What is...
- Dr. Stevens...
- Give me a second.
- You don't have a second.
ECMO is too dangerous. We're gonna
have to keep her going on epi.
It'll stop her circulation.
No point keeping her heart rate up
if she doesn't have functioning limbs.
I know that.
I'm sorry.
Let's...
We have to keep pushing epi.
It's our best option.
We'll just have to find a middle ground.
You can do this.
I can't believe you would consider
moving out of your trailer.
The view alone.
- See the mist rise off the lake.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I'm not moving.
- You're still you?
- I'm still me.
Good.
- Where's Emily?
- They took her away.
- Where? Why didn't you wake me?
- Dr. Shepherd told us not to.
What?
Where's the baby?
Dr. Stevens, she died half an hour ago.
It wasn't your fault.
You put me in charge.
I fell asleep. I killed that baby.
No, you didn't.
She was going to die anyway.
She had a restricted atrial septum
and virtually no aorta.
As soon as Dr. Burke opened up her
chest, we knew she didn't have a chance.
I don't get it.
You order me to stay the night,
take care of her.
I work my ass off doing CPR, pumping
her full of every drug on the planet.
God, do you have any idea how scared
I was? And it was all for nothing?
Hardly. This comes up again,
you'll be able to handle the pressure.
- You lied to me.
- You have to learn distance, Stevens.
You'll be a better doctor for it.
A better...
A better doctor?
I heard you worked a miracle last night.
She came around so fast I thought
the equipment was malfunctioning.
- Her SATS are completely stable.
- She's going to make it.
Go home, Grey. You've earned it.
Oh, Grey.
Way to go.
Did you hear that? Way to go.
- My baby died.
- We know.
She just... died.
I have an idea.
The first person I killed,
I was a second-year resident.
James Hanson.
You should go home, Alex.
There's nothing you can do here.
Nobody should die alone.
400 years ago
another well-known English guy
had an opinion about being alone.
John Donne.
He thought we were never alone.
Of course,
it was fancier when he said it.
Don't try and talk.
Your windpipe was perforated.
Dr. Burke repaired it
and you should be fine.
We'll keep you here
at least ten days for observation.
Make sure there's no infection.
Maybe just to be on the safe side,
we'll make it two weeks.
"No man is an island,
entire unto himself. "
- Oh, that's him.
- Yeah. That's him.
I'm Ionely, Derek.
Boil down that island talk
and he just meant that all anyone needs
is someone to step in...
... and let us know we're not alone.
Get it. Good boy.
- Ready? Good boy, Doc.
- OK.
And who's to say that someone
can't have four legs?
Someone to play with
or run around with...
High jump.
... or just hang out.
www.tvsubtitles.net