Last season on Grey's Anatomy:
You have to go. I'm late.
Seriously. Goodbye... uh...
- Derek.
- Yeah.
A month ago you were in med school
being taught by doctors.
- Today, you are the doctors.
- You're interns. Grunts.
Nobodies.
Bottom of the surgical food chain.
It's like candy, but with blood,
which is so much better.
Dr. Shepherd? He's over there.
Who feels like they have
no idea what they're doing?
- Stop looking at me like that.
- Like what?
Like you've seen me naked.
I don't get picked
'cause I slept with my boss
and didn't get into med school
'cause I have a famous mother.
I used to be a doctor, I think.
Fine, George and Izzie,
you can move in.
You blew me off
for a bottle of tequila.
It's not nearly as much fun
to wake up to.
You mind movin' this tail wagon?
The next time I see you favoring
Meredith Grey in any way,
I'll make sure she doesn't
see the inside of an OR for a month.
- I'm your boss.
- You don't scare me.
- Richard promised chief to both of us.
- Keep friends close and enemies closer.
- Morning, Dr. Model.
- Dr. Evil Spawn.
You're not the enemy.
You're just the competition.
What is this that we're doing here?
You need a definition?
There are other options.
It's a tumor.
It's pressing against your optic nerve.
You've got syphilis.
I don't know how this happened.
You and Alex?
You gave me syphilis?
Some people
would call this a relationship.
- Who?
- Me.
My God, you're falling for him.
What makes a hotshot doc
leave the Big Apple?
- Hi. I'm Addison Shepherd.
- Shepherd?
You must be the woman
who's been screwing my husband.
To be a good surgeon,
you have to think like a surgeon.
Emotions are messy.
Tuck them neatly away
and step into a clean, sterile room
where the procedure is simple.
Cut, suture and close.
You look familiar. You been here before?
Once. That worked out really well.
I know that look.
It's one of two things.
Either your boss is giving you hell
or your boyfriend is. Which is it?
Both.
But sometimes,
you're faced with a cut that won't heal.
My boyfriend is my boss,
which was a problem.
But not as big a problem as the fact
that my boyfriend has a wife.
Tell you what,
this one, it's on the house.
A cut that rips its stitches wide open.
- What are you doing here?
- Your hair's different.
- A lot of things are different.
- It's longer. It's very Russell Crowe.
- What are you doing here?
- You just pick up and leave everything?
Your house, your practice, your friends?
You had a life in Manhattan.
Had.
And now you have a girlfriend
in Seattle.
- She seems sweet.
- The ice you're on. Thin.
She's young.
That wide-eyed, he's-a-brain-surgeon
thing, but still sweet.
Which was what you were going for.
The anti-Addison?
If you came to try to win me back,
forget it.
I did. I flew across the country
to reminisce over wedding photos,
get drunk, fall into bed, and make you
realize you can't live without me.
Relax. Derek, I'm here for work.
I'm helming the TTTS case
you guys admitted last week
and from Richard's briefing...
- He knew you were coming?
- He asked me. Didn't he say?
- No. He didn't.
- Hm. Surprise.
The hair, though. You know I've
always had a thing for Russell Crowe.
Let me see it.
No lacerations, minimal swelling.
- George really knocked you around.
- He's a lightweight.
- Could've pinned him in a second.
- Why didn't you?
Are you kidding? I'm riding a career
in Plastics all the way to the bank.
Can't afford to injure these babies.
- Especially over O'Malley.
- You had it coming.
The dude punches like my sister.
So, by your definition then
you got beat up by a girl.
All hail the champ!
So my guy Alex finally got
what was coming to him.
- George knocked him down in one punch.
- I don't want to talk about it!
Brag, champ, brag! You've earned it!
Can I have a beer, please?
Let's play a game
of whose life sucks the most.
- I'll win. I always win.
- No, you don't want to play with me.
Oh, I do. I'll even go first.
Derek's married.
George, beer is dripping
from your nostrils.
- Told you I'd win.
- No, you don't win.
Did you hear me?
I said Derek is married.
As in pigheaded, adulterous,
liar married.
Nothing you could say could top that.
I'm pregnant.
I win.
Joe, you all right?
Hey, Joe!
OK. Maybe Joe wins.
- Lie down.
- The medics are coming.
- You called the gurney patrol?
- Sit back and relax.
- The hospital will run some tests...
- Tests? I don't need tests. I'm fine!
You collapsed! On the floor. It's your
bar. You know how filthy this floor is.
- Pulse is strong.
- Minor skull contusions.
- You're sleeping with someone?
- What?
- Even George got some action.
- Correction. George got some syphilis.
- How could I not know?
- Forget this.
The hospital is right across the street.
I can sure as hell
walk across the street by myself.
- I think we should...
- No, I got him. Joe!
All right.
Details. You're pregnant?
What are you gonna do?
Look, you know what happens
to pregnant interns.
I'm not switching to the vagina squad
or spending my life popping zits.
I'm too talented. Surgery's my life.
Which begs the question:
Who are you sleeping with?
- Just a guy.
- That's all I get?
You can't just bring something like this
up and expect me to drop it.
Well, watch me.
Don't you have a date with McDreamy?
- More like McMarried.
- McWhat?
I came to check on Joe.
- You think he's gonna be OK?
- Will he need an operation?
Operation, yes.
OK, hard to tell.
Basilar artery's like a balloon.
Subarachnoid bleeding.
- Aneurysm the size of a golf ball.
- No way to clip something like that.
- Not without magic fingers.
- Or a standstill operation.
You're doing a standstill...
He's doing a standstill operation.
I'd like to try. First I need
some additional patient history,
overnight labs, and a cerebral angio.
- I'm drunk.
- Meredith...
McBastard.
Ahem.
- What are you doing?
- Uh...
I am on her side. But we're talking
a possible standstill here.
Recognize.
- Meredith!
- Go away!
Just wait. We should discuss this.
Here's a thought. No!
Quit following me!
- At least let me explain.
- Explain?
You should have explained
the night we met in the bar.
Before any of the rest of it.
- That would have been a good time.
- Look, I know how you feel.
Do you? Somehow I doubt that.
Because if you did, you would shut up,
and you would turn around
and go back inside,
because you would realize that
I am this close to getting in my car
and running you down in the parking lot!
- Where're your keys?
- I'm fine!
Meredith, give me your keys.
Let's go home.
...and the husband was the...
Well, I will be back in the morning
to report for duty.
And you... get some rest.
What is she doing here?
You and I both know
she's the best in the field.
Bringing Addie out was a business
decision, nothing personal.
Oh, well, what a relief.
It's not personal. It is personal to me.
The workings of my surgical unit
don't have any...
- Don't include my wife!
- Don't include your private life!
Burke will act as chief of surgery
until I'm back on my feet.
You gave chief to Burke.
There's no room for personal
in being chief.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- You have been sleeping with an intern.
So I guess part of being chief
is personal.
Close the door on your way out.
L. S.
IV nurse call ICU, extension 323.
Babcock.
Right-angle clamp.
Oh. I'm gonna sterilize everything
when I'm done.
The scrub nurses
won't know I was here.
My lips are sealed.
Dr. Tucker to Radiology.
So, I have a question to ask.
I checked the schedule and I noticed
that you and I are both off tonight.
I made reservations.
I have a favorite restaurant.
None of those were questions.
Would you like to go out to dinner
with me tonight?
You know, the OR is the one place
where I can come and think.
I'm thinking right now, OK?
Of course.
I get it.
I'm not a violent person.
I'm a pacifist.
But, you know,
he just kept pushing and push...
He pushed me, I pushed back.
I was pushed. And now he...
If Alex tries to lay a hand on you,
just tell me, I'll take care of it.
You...
I don't need you to take care of it.
If Alex starts something
I'll handle it myself.
I can handle it.
OK, people, assignments.
Yang, you're on discharges.
O'Malley report to room E19.
Grey come see me,
and who was on call last night?
Sloppy, sloppy, sloppy.
Redo these and return them to me
before lunch, understood?
- Understood.
- Karev, don't tempt me.
- Somebody's popular.
- Meaning?
There's been a special request,
just for you.
The chief runs through all of this?
Before lunch. After, you've got calls
to return, a budget to approve,
two staff meetings, and four of
Richard's surgeries, including your own.
Absolutely. No problem.
Virgins.
So. Congratulations are in order.
Don't sweat it,
I'll only be your boss for a few days.
I'm aware of Richard's recovery time.
I operated on him, remember?
I do. He survived and chose me
to take over while recruiting your wife.
Clearly, he has brain damage.
Or is it your ex-wife?
I'm a little fuzzy on that.
- We're separated.
- Sorry to interrupt, Dr. Burke.
- You're never interrupting.
- She always is.
I was checking to see if Dr. Burke
secured the intern...
The intern you requested? He did.
Define TTTS.
Twin-twin transfusion syndrome.
Conjoined fetal twins.
Connected by?
- Blood vessels in the placenta.
- Meaning?
One twin gets too much blood,
the other too little, endangering both.
I'd expect you to know that, Grey.
You said probably nothing could be done.
TTTS is usually impossible to correct.
Unless you are one of a handful
of surgeons in the world
who knows how to separate
fetal blood vessels.
Which, luckily for you, I am.
So we'll get you into surgery tomorrow.
If you have any questions at all,
please ask Dr. Grey.
From what I have seen, she is one of
the hospital's most popular interns.
I could've answered your question
given a chance.
Chin up. I'm this tough on everyone, not
just the women my husband sleeps with.
Order an ultrasound for her
and pre-op labs in...
Hi. Can I have the chart
for E19, please? Thank you.
Oh, good, you're here.
Let's get started.
OK.
- O'Malley.
- Yeah?
- You're touching me.
- Yeah.
No. Carmen...
I want you to listen to me
very carefully.
As long as I'm in here, I don't know
what's happening out there.
With my doctors.
My patients. My hospital.
You are my eyes today. My ears.
- I want you to be a sponge.
- A sponge?
You report any and everything
happening in this hospital to me.
- I'm an investigative sponge.
- I'm not fooling around.
There's too much been happening lately
under my radar.
It stops today.
IV nurse, call ICU extension 3231.
Burke. You gave Grey to Addison.
Are you sure about that?
That's not your call, Shepherd.
And for the record, I'm always sure.
Did you need me?
As the new chief, I'm...
- Interim chief.
- "Chief" nonetheless.
Ever attempt a standstill surgery?
It's the location of
the aneurysm that makes it tricky.
Your body temperature would be lowered
to protect it and stop the heart.
Which stops blood flow to the brain
which reduces the risk of rupture.
I'll have 45 minutes
to clip the aneurysm.
- Before I get the heart started again.
- You wanna freeze my body,
- drain my blood, and stop my heart?
- And bring you back.
- In under 45 minutes?
- Right.
- If you go over, is it free?
- No.
Dr. Yang, you can go and handle
the pre-op labs now.
How much?
How much does something like this cost?
Don't worry about that right now.
Look, you guys say that you can kill me
and bring me back, I believe you.
You're doctors, but I own a bar.
I don't got any insurance so I'm not
that concerned about the surgery
so much as what I'm gonna do
when I survive it.
I need a number. Ten grand? Twenty?
- Thirty?
- It's a couple hundred at least.
At least.
Who's Halloran?
Patient in 4115.
-  Dr. Cole, call the OR.
- Red hair?
Wife knits all the time?
He had the colectomy?
Ah, colon dude. That's right.
Who's Monterroso?
4238. Mom with the really cute kids.
She spiked a post-op fever.
You spent two hours with her.
Hernia chick. That's right.
You've treated them for a week
and you don't know their names?
In Surgery we don't waste time
getting to know the patients.
- They're meat, we're butchers.
- They're humans.
You do know what a human is,
Evil Spawn?
I'm not evil.
Unless evil turns you on.
Do you ever wake up, realize nobody
likes you, and, I don't know, care?
Oh.
I think somebody likes me.
Hey.
What, you don't speak
now you're chief? Burke!
- What do you want?
- What?
What do you want?
You don't want to go out to dinner.
You don't want to meet me in the on-call
room, and you don't want to talk to me.
I could pretend I know, but I don't
have your home phone number.
- So tell me, what do you want?
- Don't yell at me.
- We're having a conversation.
- What do you want?
I don't know!
Figure it out.
What's the report?
No report. It's very quiet today, sir.
There's no gossip?
Surgeries I should know about?
- Now come on, what's the buzz?
- You know, not in halls, not in OR.
Not in the stairwells.
Especially nothing happening in the,
you know... They're just stairwells.
They told me you were in a nightgown,
but I thought I'd come see.
Very nice, huh.
Heard O'Malley laid you out cold.
Nice eye.
- Whoa, who sent that?
- We all pitched in. The whole floor.
Well, please,
tell the whole floor a big thank you.
Yeah, I will.
Alex, you gotta get me out of here, man.
Get me transferred to County Hospital.
Not County. Here, they can kill you
and bring you back,
but at County,
they can just kill you. No joke.
I can't afford this place, man.
I'm gonna lose the bar.
- Hey, Joe, how you doing?
- Hey, Scooter.
OK. That's mine?
- We'll start by saving your life.
- The bar is my life. You know that.
You've been at last call
every night since you moved here.
I'm gonna have to shut it down
or sell it.
You can't do that.
Place is an institution.
I've owned the bar across the street
for 14 years,
and I've never been
inside this hospital till now.
I'll pay my tab. That's gotta be
good for something. How much is it?
Close to a grand.
How about I pay, like, 60?
That's good.
And I'll pay you back later.
Hey, champ!
Orderly, please report to station
three. Orderly, report to station three.
What does it take
to go after another woman's husband?
- Excuse me?
- It happened to me.
Jeff moved in with a long-legged
miniskirt who answers his phones
three weeks into my pregnancy.
That gel is really cold.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry about your husband.
Are you sorry about
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd's husband?
I'm going to be checking
a few things today.
I bet she asked to work with you.
It's what I would have done.
I'm gonna go check on your labs.
Heya, sunshine.
Deep breath.
Morning sickness must suck.
Just so we're clear,
do not breathe a word of what you heard
last night to anyone.
Not about me. Not about Meredith. Not
about Meredith and Dr. McDreamy...
- Hey, Dr. Burke.
- Joe.
Um, vital signs stable overnight.
Today's CT shows no re-bleeding.
The EKG...
shows...
um, normal sinus rhythm.
No ischemia, no dysrhythmias.
Looking good.
Page me if there are any changes.
Oh, hi, Chief.
No, not much going on.
Other than your interim chief making out
with my friend in the stairwell,
but, hey... Sponge duty sucks.
- You talking to yourself now?
- Yes. No!
Damn it, I'm a bad sponge.
A leaky sponge.
I'm gonna leak all the wrong secrets.
I'm a bad liar,
can't even lie about talking to myself.
You look nice today.
Wore my new lip gloss
'cause my ex-boyfriend's wife looks like
Isabella freakin' Rossellini,
and I'm like... me.
I'm trying to outdo her when she's
the victim here. How crazy is that?
Not crazy. Smart.
You know, gloss, you know,
prevents chapped lips and... you...
Ex-boyfriend?
I'm an evil mistress.
Well, still. You look nice.
Thanks. What are you doing here?
Come on, O'Malley. Out with it.
OK. Can you think of any reason,
any reason at all, really,
why Cristina would be kissing Burke?
After all this time. All your warnings
about me sleeping with my boss,
- and you're doing the same thing?
- It's not the same.
- It's the same...
- You two are in a relationship.
And you and Burke are in?
Switzerland. It's very neutral there.
And they make very nice watches.
Have you even bothered to tell Burke
about the baby?
- Are you going to?
- Look, Meredith, can we not go there?
Can everyone just accept that
I like to keep some things to myself?
- I don't discuss everything to death.
- Well, why even confide in me at all
if you're so intent
on not discussing it?
Why even tell me?
When I found out about the miniskirt,
I called her up and took her to lunch.
It was perfectly civil.
I said I didn't hold it against her,
that these things happened. But, really?
I wanted to put a face on the bitch
that got my husband to throw away
15 years of marriage.
- Got a second?
- Depends on what you need.
Who the hell is Dr. McDreamy?
Me. I'm Dr. McDreamy.
I'm tall, handsome.
I lean against things and ponder the
difficulties of dating beautiful women.
I'm trying to be a surgeon here!
- That took a lot of nerve.
- She came highly recommended.
- Right.
- So you don't recommend her?
- I did not say that.
- Just not her medical skills.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Yes?
Labs confirm what look like
abnormalities on the ultrasound.
- I think you should come and see.
- Fine. Let's go.
- Meredith. Meredith...
- Don't.
Any available IV nurse to OR Two.
Well, no report.
You know, same nothing as earlier.
I should go.
Oh, actually there is something, sir.
- Burke and Shepherd marking territory?
- No, sir.
It's about Joe. The bartender.
The standstill patient.
See. Bilateral pleural effusion
with evidence of subQ edema.
In English, please?
We've detected what looks like
beginning heart failure in the twins.
- Don't be alarmed.
- Are my babies gonna be OK?
I'm going to take you into surgery now.
Book the OR.
Move.
Tell Pete to wash out the taps
every night. Not every other night.
And remind him that the delivery truck
comes at 6:00a. m. Kegs go in the back.
Oh, another thing. There's petty cash
on the top shelf in the storage closet.
We're operating on patients. That's it.
- I know, but...
- I sympathize. I do.
But solving Joe's finances
is not my job, it's not your job,
and it's sure as hell not the job
I assigned you today.
It seems wrong to cut him open, sew him
up, and leave him, left with nothing.
If we can save his life, we'll hardly
be leaving him with nothing.
That's as far as I can go for now.
Let's start cooling him.
Can't see much from back here, O'Malley.
I know. I'm trying to find a loophole
to help Joe.
- You know Joe?
- Oh, yeah.
I was the only female intern my year.
I didn't know anybody
and nobody knew me except Joe.
He knew me.
Oh. So, you and Joe?
All you people ever think about
is how to get into somebody's pants.
You're nasty.
That's why you got syphilis.
Joe was the first person here
to say I'd make a good surgeon.
Not that he knew anything about it.
But it was somethin' when I had nothin'.
Oh, sure. I'm the guy with the heart
of stone and you brought snacks.
- It's a working lunch.
- Snacks to watch Joe die.
He's not gonna "die" die.
They'll bring him back.
He is going to "die" die.
No "pulse" pulse. He'll be "dead" dead.
It's a granola bar, Alex.
Not a bag of supersize popcorn
and a box of chocolate movie mints.
That's it.
Dead!
Excuse me.
Julie, we're gonna go in
laparoscopically.
You're not gonna feel anything.
And neither are the twins.
OK, let's get going!
Ten blade.
Begin with a three-millimeter incision.
- We stop the blood flow?
- To protect the brain.
Operate in a bloodless field
so the aneurysm won't rupture.
- And cool the body?
- To induce hypothermia.
Keeps the tissue viable
until the blood is restored.
Body temp is at 60 degrees.
OK, Joe. Time to die.
Flatline.
- We've got 45 minutes, people.
- Start the clock.
Got it.
So what's your "Joe" story?
Seems like everybody here has one.
You first.
OK. I went to Joe's place
the night before I started working here.
I'd only been in town,
you know, a few days.
I met a woman. I got drunk
and she took advantage of me.
Or she got drunk
and I took advantage of her.
I got drunk and she took...
No. We were drunk. Definitely.
Somebody took advantage. Either way, I
look at it as my initiation to Seattle.
- What about you?
- Oh, I don't have one.
I just wanted to hear yours.
So, technically, the paperwork
just needs to be submitted
by midnight of the day of the surgery
to be considered?
Oh, good.
Well, thank you very much. Thanks.
How you doing there, Grey?
Good. I'm good.
You know, I'm very sweet
once you get to know me.
- No, you're not.
- We could be good friends.
- Alex. Never, ever. Ever.
- Why not?
Give me one reason why we could?
What about you is even remotely human?
It's going too slowly.
- I hope Joe can pull through this.
- He can. He will. He has to.
Damn it.
I can't get the clamp to hold.
Give me the bipolars.
I'm gonna go in at a different angle.
Time remaining?
- Irrigation, please.
- 17 minutes.
Shepherd, I need eight minutes
to get him back, to warm him up.
Time to make
the next 17 minutes count.
Right there, go in from there. See it?
See, that's why we can't
do it right there.
He's dead. Technically.
Which is science,
and this is a huge thing.
So some research foundation
has to be interested.
So, in essence, you want to donate
Joe's body to science?
At least for the next 17 minutes.
- "Privately funded grant."
- For educational purposes.
We're a teaching hospital.
The standstill surgery qualifies.
I didn't peg you for the type
to ignore my instructions.
All due respect, sir, it's worth a shot.
It's someone's life.
It's always someone's life, O'Malley.
You're hovering.
- You can leave now.
- OK.
Eight minutes.
We need to start rewarming, Shepherd.
Take the bipolars, please. Thank you.
Shepherd,
we need to start warming him up, now!
- Hang on.
- Now. I need it now, Shepherd.
I can't seem to get...
I just can't get behind the aneurysm.
If I could get behind the aneurysm,
I could... There it is.
Got it. That's it.
- Are you sure?
- I'm always sure.
Good work, everybody.
It's all yours there, Chief.
OK, let's grab Joe
before he decides to go into the light.
Start warming him up.
Clamps are coming off.
Turn the pump on.
Watch cerebral perfusion pressures.
Keep M. A. P. at greater than 60, please.
I know
you're enjoying yourself, Preston.
It's a power kick to be the chief.
You're never more surrounded.
Never more alone.
You're everyone's father,
everyone's boss, and no one's friend.
Choices you make.
Clean slices and neat stitches.
No emotions, no compromise,
no personal life.
- But, Richard...
- I just had brain surgery.
I'm surrounded by fruit baskets.
The only people who've been in this room
come and kiss my ass.
I gave you a shot for a reason, Preston.
You and I, we're the same.
We put the job first.
That was the single most amazing surgery
I have ever witnessed.
You, you killed a man
and brought him back to life.
You, like, raised the dead.
God, how does that feel?
Are you rushing? Is it...
Like you wouldn't believe.
Hey, do you still have those
reservations? 'Cause I'm starving.
Cristina, I think there's something
we should discuss.
Yeah. Yeah, there is.
It's pretty clear.
It is?
We've been fooling ourselves
to think that we can continue
without consequences.
Consequences...
We have careers to think about.
Reputations.
We both put the job first.
You are very focused. I respect that.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Any available IV nurse to OR two.
Oh, you're ending this?
I think it's best to make a clean break.
OK.
Before it gets too involved.
Before it gets...
Messy. Right, right. That would be bad.
It's nothing personal.
Get in here, O'Malley.
OK. I tried. I really tried.
But there's a lot of stuff happening
out there. Stuff I can't tell you.
Stuff I won't tell you.
Crazy stuff.
Stuff I'm gonna have nightmares about.
But I'm not gonna tell you
about any of it.
Because it doesn't matter.
Not when there's a guy
who we all know and love
who's gonna be bankrupt because
he needed a surgery to save his life.
- I spent the whole day on it.
- O'Malley...
Let me finish.
You're wrong, sir.
Now you can fire me, or bring me up
on disciplinary action or whatever.
I'm telling you, Joe deserves...
Deserves our help.
Couldn't help yourself, could you?
Whether or not it'd win you any points,
even from me.
I signed your request.
Give it to Patricia,
she'll know what to do.
- Joe may keep his bar after all.
- Thank you, sir.
- O'Malley!
- Yes?
Yell at me again,
and I'll snap you like a twig.
Yes, sir.
See? Just a small scar.
And my babies?
Dr. Cole, call the OR.
Your babies are doing very well.
And Dr. Grey will be back
to check on you a little bit later.
I'd prefer it if Dr. Grey
were taken off the case.
Why, is there a problem?
Just reminds me of someone I don't like.
Someone my husband likes a lot.
Particularly in lingerie.
You understand.
No, no, I don't understand.
Well, she's sleeping
with your husband, right?
Ms. Philips,
I lack Dr. Grey's class and patience
so, let me set the record straight.
My husband didn't cheat on me,
I cheated on him.
So the wronged woman here, Dr. Grey.
So, I think you owe her
one hell of an apology.
One night I parked my car,
I unlock my front door, go inside
my house, and something's different.
Nothing's different,
everything's the same
but yet, still, something's different.
And I stand there for a while.
And then I know.
See, there are moments for me, you know,
usually when I'm in the OR,
when I just know
what's gonna happen next.
So I go upstairs.
As I walk down the hall, I try
to prepare myself for what I'm gonna see
when I go into my bedroom.
I step on a man's jacket
that doesn't belong to me.
And everything
I think I know... just shifts.
Because the jacket that doesn't belong
to me is a jacket that I recognize.
And what I know now is
that when I go into my bedroom,
I'm not just gonna see
that my wife is cheating on me.
I'm gonna see that my wife
is cheating on me with Mark,
who happened to be my best friend.
It's just so pedestrian,
common and dirty,
and cruel.
Mostly just cruel.
I left. Came out here.
- And you met me.
- And I met you.
Well, what was I to you?
The girl you screwed
to get over being screwed?
You were like coming up for fresh air.
It's like I was drowning
and you saved me.
That's all I know.
It's not enough.
They say practice makes perfect.
Theory is,
the more you think like a surgeon
the more you become one.
The better you get
at remaining neutral, clinical.
Cut, suture, close.
And the harder
it becomes to turn it off...
Thought I might see
your ugly mug in here tonight.
Did you hear the good news?
... to stop thinking like a surgeon.
O'Malley!
I heard what you did, champ.
And remember what it means
to think like a human being.
The clinic has a policy.
They wouldn't let me
confirm my appointment
unless I designated
an emergency contact person.
Someone to be there, just in case,
and to help me home, you know, after.
Anyway, I put your name down.
That's why I told you I'm pregnant.
You're my "person."
I am?
Yeah, you are.
Whatever.
He dumped me.
You realize this constitutes hugging?
Shut up.
I'm your "person."
www.tvsubtitles.net