Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
I'm mind-blowingly good in bed.
Then he sleeps with Olivia
instead of me.
I'm having a baby too.
Yes, I am. A little boy.
- You lied to me.
- You'll be a better doctor for it.
I'm Ionely, Derek.
I can't.
When Derek broke up with you,
I was there.
All I ever am is there for you guys
and the one time I need you...
- Are you OK?
- I failed the medical boards.
Karev, it's over. You screwed up.
If I retake the exam and I don't pass...
You will no longer be a surgical
resident at Seattle Grace.
It's an urban myth that
suicide rates spike at the holidays.
Turns out, they actually go down.
Experts think it's because people
are less inclined to off themselves
when surrounded by family.
Looks like Santa threw up in here.
Just go with it, we're being supportive.
Oh, hey. What do you think?
Did I go too overboard?
Oh, I know sometimes
I can go a little overboard.
- No, we love it.
- It's great.
Oh, yay. I love Christmas.
- We know.
- Clearly.
Ironically,
that same family togetherness
is thought to be the reason
that depression rates
actually do spike at the holidays.
Yeah, OK, Izzie doesn't count.
Oh, I thought you might like
to help me decorate it tonight.
Mark our first Christmas together.
I'm Jewish.
Seriously?
- My stepfather, Saul Rubenstein?
- Oh, right.
Right.
Look at her belly.
She's almost as wide as she is tall.
Are her ankles swollen?
Is that why she's waddling?
- What happens when she leaves?
- She's going on leave?
What do you think happens when people
push babies out their vaginas?
- Think we'll get a new resident?
- Nah.
They'll let us wander unattended.
- See how much damage we can do.
- Yeah, well, you would know.
We should all get together and get
Bailey a Christmas gift for the baby.
Or we could organize
a Secret Santa thing.
- Listen, Tiny Tim, you can take your...
- Secret Santa sounds great, Izzie.
OK.
We're being supportive.
Hey.
Hey. You OK? You seem...
Yeah. You know...
- Holidays.
- Oh.
Yeah. I do know.
Tim Epstein, 38,
fell off the roof of his house.
I was stringing Hanumas lights
and a shingle came loose.
- Hanumas?
- Hanumas. Christmukkah. We go all out.
- Awesome.
- He fell twelve feet.
The good news is, my head broke my fall.
There are no visible deformities,
but he's having
some focal left arm weakness.
He'll probably be fine.
He's always been a little hard-headed.
- Does your head hurt when you laugh?
- Is that a bad thing?
Do you wanna follow my finger
with your eyes, please?
- I know karate.
- Huh?
Uh...
Your husband might need a little quiet,
so, there's a cafeteria...
No, no. Whoa. Let 'em stay.
Pain or no, I don't want to
miss out on the holidays with my kids.
Who would like to take
Mr. Epstein down for a CT?
Stevens it is.
- You should have a dog.
- No dog.
Come on, get a dog.
Nadia Shelton, 41, scheduled
for excision of her gastric ulcer.
Lot of good it's done.
She's been scheduled for three days.
Mom, it's not his fault.
Every day she gets rescheduled
for emergencies.
- We are sorry for the inconvenience.
- Inconvenience?
Watch your child spend 3 days in pain,
then talk to me about inconvenience.
We get a lot of trauma cases
at the holidays.
- Your daughter's ulcer is non-emergent.
- Is that the news?
Are you saying my wife's not important?
Is that what I hear?
- When are you taking her?
- It's not the remote.
We have reservations
to eat at the Space Needle.
- We've had 'em for months.
- All right!
Prep Mrs. Shelton
for her ulcer excision,
- which will happen this morning.
- Thank you!
Ernie, I'm so happy!
We're gonna go to the Needle!
Grey, Karev: cover the pit.
You can expect all sorts of holiday
idiocy so that is my gift to you.
- Yang...
- Dr. Bailey.
UNOS called.
They have a donor heart for my patient.
- Heart surgery? I'm free.
- I'm available.
No, you're not. You're covering the pit.
- Yang, it's yours.
- Thank you.
Pit!
Damn. Heart transplant.
Woulda liked to have seen that.
- There's tomorrow.
- Maybe for you.
- Meaning?
- I retake the boards tomorrow.
Pretty sure I'm gonna fail,
which makes today my last day here,
and I get to spend it
doing stitches in the pit.
- So, when does Hanukkah fall this year?
- Uh... No idea.
If there are other traditions
you want me to be aware...
Oh, no, Burke, seriously,
I haven't observed religious holidays
since I was old enough to know better.
"Run as fast as you can.
You can catch him..."
- Good morning, Justin, Marion.
- Good morning.
Hi, Dr. Burke.
I'm here with good news. Great news.
- You don't mean that...
- UNOS called. We have a heart.
- I'll operate this morning.
- You hear that, baby?
Santa Claus is bringing you
a new heart for Christmas.
Tell the fat-ass
to give it to someone else.
I don't want it.
I'm sorry, Dr. Burke. He's tired today.
I'm tired every day.
I hate Christmas every day.
I'd rather not have
another stupid operation.
Justin, I know surgery can be
frightening, but you need this heart.
- You've worn out your last one.
- His last one?
Justin had a heart transplant as a baby,
but his heart hasn't aged
as well as he has.
You understand that, Justin?
Your heart can't keep up with you
anymore. You need a new one.
I don't care. I don't want it.
Can you tell me why not?
Dr. Kim, 1471.
- Anxiety attacks, aneurysms and ulcers.
- Must be December.
- Chief, Adele just called.
- Tell her I'm...
She knows you're not in surgery.
And she said to tell you, quote,
"We are going to our niece's
school pageant this morning."
"You have known about it for months."
"After what you pulled
on Thanksgiving..."
Then she started using many words
that I don't feel comfortable repeating.
- I have seven surgeons on vacation...
- There was something about "divorce."
You'll have to cover my ulcer excision.
Yes, sir.
The woman is unreasonable.
When did watching a six-year-old
dressed up like a wise man...
You couldn't hang up the phone?
Male, 44. Had a gastric bypass.
Three weeks post-op.
Reported pain when we found him.
- Said something about fruitcake.
- He must have torn his abdomen.
- You'll have to fight me for this one.
- He's all yours. My parting gift.
OK, for your mom, I got a lambswool
blanket, handmade in Edinburgh.
It's soft, comfortable, says "don't hate
me for hurting your son" with fabric.
- You know my mom loves you.
- No, she used to.
I gotta make up ground with these gifts.
- So, what do you think, plain or plaid?
- I don't know. Whatever.
- You love Christmas shopping.
- I'm not in the mood for it right now.
How about French food and
Scottish catalogues tonight around nine?
- Well, I guess that depends...
- Come on.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yeah?
- I have Tim Epstein's CT scans.
- Ah, good.
- OK, what do you think?
- It's not great.
Oh, no, it's not great at all.
Honey bunny, what do you think of this?
Excuse me,
I need to take her blood pressure.
- What is the guy saying?
- I got three arch-moguls on my ass.
- Josh...
- Language! Josh!
- Any questions about the surgery?
- Apart from when you're gonna do it?
- We're doing it now.
- Good.
- Sorry.
- Don't apologize.
- Do you have any questions?
- No.
I've had three bleeding ulcers
in the last five years.
Yeah. I hope you read the chart.
- Yes.
- Good.
- A gastric perforation just came in.
- Damn.
All right,
take Mrs. Shelton back to her room.
- Seriously?
- Do I look like I'm kidding?
We'll get to her this afternoon.
Grey, call the ER, tell them
to send him up, and then scrub in.
Alex Karev failed his boards,
and he's retaking them tomorrow.
He can't study for a practical
by himself. If he fails again, he's out.
OK, go.
- O'Malley.
- Yeah?
After you drop her off,
get back here and scrub in.
- All right.
- OK.
- OK, Justin.
- I don't want the heart.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because you need it.
And until you're 18,
your mother calls all the shots.
My mother's a liar. You heard.
She said the heart came from Santa.
- She shouldn't decide anything.
- Well, you could make a run for it,
but the heart you have
won't get you very far.
- Are we ready?
- Just about.
How about you, buddy? Are you ready?
If I die in the surgery, can you
give this heart to some other kid?
Not gonna happen, Justin.
Not on my watch.
Here we go.
...and it was only one day of oil.
- And then what happened?
- It lasted eight whole days and nights.
- And it was a miracle.
- I wanted to say that part.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- You remember Dr. Shepherd?
- Should we talk more privately?
- Just tell us, is it bad?
- The fall caused a subdural hematoma.
- I don't even know what that means.
- That means, your dad...
- His brain is bleeding.
- Great.
There is some risk to the surgery,
but it has to happen
- before the bleeding gets worse.
- What kind of risks?
The bleed is in an area of the brain
that controls speech and motor control.
- We don't need an operation. OK?
- You know, Jake, I think we do.
- But, hey, you know something?
- What?
We have a doctor named "Shepherd."
"Shepherd."
Is that a sign from God, or what?
Look at that.
Beautiful fit.
Now we have to figure out
why he's so angry.
If I had that mother, I'd be angry too.
- Actually, I do have that mother.
- His mother is not the problem.
- She loves him. She never leaves.
- She also never listens.
- She doesn't know him.
- Justin's depressed. You heard.
He doesn't want to live.
I just hope he changes his mind
before he's too late.
What do you mean, "too late"?
With all medical realities being equal,
why does one patient live
and another dies?
I believe there's
a mind-body-spirit connection.
And if Justin really doesn't want
this heart, his body will reject it.
OK, let me get this straight.
You don't just celebrate Christmas,
you actually believe in Santa Claus?
Dr. Yang, go and schedule
a psychiatric consult for our patient.
- But we're not done here.
- You are.
I don't know.
It hurts here and here and back here.
Did you get hit by a truck
and forget about it?
You're judged on bedside manner.
I wouldn't be surprised
if that's why you failed.
Could you be more patronizing?
- I didn't ask for your help.
- Enough with the ego, you big baby.
I gave up a surgery for this.
Now, like I said,
it hurts here and here and back here.
Oh, and this morning,
I noticed my poop
was a funny grayish color.
Wow.
That's all you can save of his stomach?
If eating is what this man lives for,
we should put him out of his misery.
Paging Dr. Karevian.
What did you just say?
Just... it's a joke.
Kevorkian, Karevian.
- Alex Karev.
- I get the joke.
I just don't think it's funny.
You see this, O'Malley?
I make one mistake with this scalpel
and this man's dead.
My husband, he makes mistakes
at his job all the time.
As far as I know he's never killed
anyone, but I have, and you will.
And Alex did.
He made a math mistake
and a man died for it.
Run that past your accountant,
see how he'd feel if every mistake
he made, someone ended up dead.
You don't have to like Alex
or care about him.
But you damn well
have to be on his side.
Hold that.
What a great family.
"Hanumas," "Christmukkah..."
And how cute are those kids?
Really, Dr. Stevens. "Christmukkah"?
I think it's sweet.
Know what time of year
neurosurgeons are busiest?
No. There's a "time of year"?
There's no hard or fast rule,
but brain injuries tend to pile up
around holidays. Like our friend here.
Folks fall off their roofs
while they string up lights
or go skating for the first time
in a decade, break their heads open.
And every year, people drive
through blizzards to get to parties
where they kiss germ-infected strangers
under poisonous mistletoe.
Then they get so drunk
that they smash their heads
through the windshield
on the way home.
Like I said,
there's no hard or fast rule.
- Does this hurt, Mrs. Grey?
- Yes, doctor.
- How about here? Does it hurt here?
- Yes, it does.
If you're Ionely, there are excellent
vibrators. I can give you a catalogue.
- He failed his boards. I'm helping him.
- Failed your practical?
- Glad you can keep a secret.
- I kept it. It did you no good.
- He needs our help.
- You're not serious.
If it were you?
- It wouldn't be.
- But what if it were?
- I have to go.
Be a patient. Do it for me.
When Tiny Tim goes Norman Bates
on us I'm blaming you.
- Diagnosis?
- Gallstones.
Yes.
I'm a 55-year-old man,
I'm nauseous, and I'm throwing up.
I didn't ask for any help.
OK, Evil Spawn, you can nurse
your pride, key word being "nurse",
or you can pass your test
and be a doctor. Up to you.
- Any abdominal pain?
- Yes,
from my giant fat belly
all the way to my back.
Oh, and I'm drunk. Hiccup, hiccup.
I got another one for you.
He tried to gift wrap
a 70-inch TV for his wife?
- Hernia?
- Strangulated. Pretty ugly.
And you just know the wife hates TV.
Grey, is that other project covered?
- I think so.
- Then scrub in.
O'Malley, go tell Nadia Shelton
she's off the schedule until tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Another day won't kill me, Jimmy.
- Tomorrow for sure.
- Today was "for sure".
What's he saying?
- They can't operate until tomorrow!
- Outrageous!
I cannot believe this!
Could you please turn that down?
Your mother needs to rest.
Who are you, my dad?
- Sir, please tell your son...
- Don't talk to me about my son.
- Who the hell do you think you are?
- Sorry.
I just think that your wife should rest.
- I can't go Christmas shopping...
- You messed me up.
You people have ruined everything.
I hope you're happy.
Again, very sorry.
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- "Very sorry."
That cuts it here, doc, thanks a lot.
Yeah. OK, the way
you're grabbing me now, it's assault.
This... is an exam. Pads.
What... What the hell? Does Izzie
know... Does Burke know about this?
Unbunch your panties, George.
We're helping Alex study. Do it.
I can't hear you
when his hand is on your boob.
Take your hand off my boob, Alex.
Thank you. Study for what?
- Shut it, Yang.
- Alex failed his boards.
- Seriously?
- I failed one part of one board.
Still, that's pretty embarrassing.
Hey, he's all yours, Georgie.
Do your worst.
You're not giving me a rectal.
Do not ask me to cough.
Dr. Cohen to Radiology.
You paged me?
I didn't see a psych consult
scheduled here.
I couldn't get one. I tried to, but
they told me to come back in January.
You disrespected me.
You mocked me in my OR.
- That can't happen.
- I... It won't happen again.
You equated my spirituality
with a belief in Santa Claus.
Burke, science is the one thing,
you know,
it's the one thing we have in common.
I'm an intern, you're not.
I'm a slob and you're not.
I say I want to keep
our relationship private
and you tell the Chief of Surgery
and you ask me to move in with you.
- And now, you're religious.
- Spiritual. There's a difference.
Well, not to me.
I don't know what we're doing.
Well, right now, we're working.
Page me if he spikes a fever.
Tell Mrs. Davison to hire a therapist,
or a priest.
Anyone Justin will talk to.
- Mrs. Epstein?
- Oh.
- How is he?
- He's gonna be fine.
- He's still groggy.
- My dad wants to see me now, OK?
- OK. Come on.
- OK.
- Run-run-run.
- Yeah, let's run-run-run.
Let's run and see Dad.
It's OK, guys, Daddy's OK.
Daddy. Daddy.
I could kiss it better, Daddy.
Jillian, I have a headache.
- I'll sing, Daddy.
- No.
- ~ Dashing through the snow...
- No, Leah.
Damn it, Leah, shut up!
I can't stand that insipid song!
- Tim.
- Just get out! Get out!
Get the hell out of here, all of you!
You stupid shepherd!
You broke my dad's brain!
How did that happen? His personality...
You didn't go near the frontal lobe.
Well,
the CT might have missed something.
It could be a reaction from anesthesia
wearing off, could be the pain.
He was in pain before surgery.
Watch him for two hours.
If he doesn't improve, get a new CT.
OK.
Dr. Stevens?
You had his brain open, literally open,
he was laying there
unconscious and vulnerable...
I poisoned him
with my anti-holiday venom?
You say there's a lot
about the brain we don't know.
How do you know your words
didn't speak to him unconsciously?
I mean, he trusted you to be his...
shepherd.
Dr. Stevens,
you should be a little embarrassed.
- I am.
- Good.
Oh, this is the CCU,
there are no trees allowed in the CCU.
I know, but it's never
really been enforced, so...
How's he doing?
Surgery went smoothly,
but it's too soon to tell.
He's really a good boy. You just met
him at a difficult time. He's been down.
I don't know why. But Father Michael
will be able to talk to him.
No offense, but your son doesn't
seem to be a fan of the holidays.
He doesn't believe in Santa.
Yes, well, a mother's job
is to protect her child's innocence.
And this Christmas
could be his last time, so...
That's what you said last year,
and the year before that.
Oh, my baby, you're awake.
You look great.
My big strong boy.
Santa brought you back to me.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, CCU regulations.
- Are we using mesh?
- Yes, the conjoined tendon is...
Dr. Bailey?
Just wouldn't want to throw up
in the body cavity.
- Dr. Bailey, are you all right?
- Oh, no.
- Do you need...
- Just... I need a minute, Grey.
When you operate,
the rest of the world goes away.
Hunger, thirst, pain:
you don't feel it in the OR.
But it's not that way when you're
sharing your body with another person.
OK. All right.
Do you have a retractor?
Sure you don't want me
to find someone to take over?
What I want you to find me
is a strawberry milk shake, extra-thick.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Nausea.
Comes with the hunger, Grey. Go.
My throat, it's like, wicked sore, yo.
Plus, I got all these sick break outs,
right?
Dude, seriously.
All right, all right!
Sit down, sit down.
Open up your mouth,
I'd like to inspect your tonsils.
Aaaa!
What's wrong with you? Are you sick?
Fake sick.
I failed my practical board exam.
O'Malley's helping me study.
- You failed your... You're helping him?
- Just to study. Nothing else.
- Izzie...
- Don't say my name!
And you are unbelievable!
I was doing mono,
the fever and glands thing.
The acne was just the teenager thing.
Izzie, would you wait?
I say I like the guy,
and you can't stop hating him.
Then as soon as he screws me over,
you're his new best friend.
He failed his boards. This is important.
- He cheated on me.
- Busted?
- Yeah, I'm busted.
- His exam is tomorrow.
You're in on this too?
- He cheated on me! God!
- Told you she'd find out.
- Of course you're in on this.
- She let him touch her boobs!
He cheated on me
with George's skanky syph nurse!
- That is just plain rude!
- We know he cheated on you!
That's why we let you turn
the living room into Santa's Village.
- What?
- We're not big on holidays.
You know that. We're being supportive
because you're having a hard time.
But right now, Alex,
he's having a harder time.
Why does everybody care
what kind of time Alex is having?
Because he's dirty Uncle Sal.
- Sorry? Huh?
- You lost me.
Dirty Uncle Sal, who embarrasses
everyone at family reunions
and who can't be left alone
with the teenage girls
but you invite him to the picnic anyway.
- What?
- Still lost.
I have a mother
who doesn't recognize me.
As far as family goes,
this hospital, you guys are it.
So, I know you're pissed at Alex,
but maybe you could try
to help him anyway.
Sort of like
in the spirit of this holiday
you keep shoving down
everybody's throats.
- You...
- What?
- "Boob?"
-  Dr. Scott to cath lab.
Somebody get in here. Doctor! Now!
Do something.
Deep breaths.
We're taking you to surgery.
Prep her now.
- It's about time.
- Sorry, I got sidetracked.
Nadia Shelton's ulcer perforated.
She's vomiting blood by the pint.
Is the chief back?
- I haven't seen him.
- No.
All right, both of you, scrub in.
I'm gonna need all the help I can get.
Well, there it is.
Left side of his frontal lobe.
- Why didn't we see that before?
- Intracerebral bleeds
- can have a delayed presentation.
- Right. You wanna get him out of there?
Just prep an OR.
I'm gonna talk to his wife.
Dr. Stevens.
Nice talking to you.
Think she'll ever talk to me again?
Am I invisible?
I'm feeling strangely invisible.
- Also inaudible.
- What?
Another surgery?
So, I guess dinner-shopping is out?
Yeah.
It's not gonna happen tonight. Sorry.
You're not.
I'm trying to figure out why you're not.
- It's Christmas, Derek.
- Yeah, I know.
It's our season. What is going on?
Are you mad? Depressed? What?
No. Mr. Epstein here is depressed.
He's bleeding from his frontal lobe.
Everything's fine, we're fine, Addie.
I'll see you at home. OK?
You need a second surgery, Mr. Epstein.
The frontal lobe is difficult.
We may be able to improve things,
but you should be prepared for the
possibility that things could get worse.
That's great.
That's just great.
I'm so glad we came to this hospital so
I could be treated by a bunch of quacks
who don't know their asses
from the inside of my skull.
Can I talk to you?
This isn't my husband.
This is not my husband.
He doesn't speak to me,
or anyone, this way.
I know this is difficult,
but the important thing right now
is that we stop the bleeding.
He's the love of my life.
And I know that
you have a lot of other patients
and you do a lot of other surgeries.
But he's the love of my life.
I just... I just need your word
that you will treat this change
in my husband's personality as
seriously as you would a fatal cancer.
Because that's the way
this feels to me and to my kids.
We were happy. We were a happy family.
It just... If you could just fix it.
Just fix it.
Mrs. Epstein, I'm gonna do
everything in my power, all right?
OK?
I didn't want it.
I already got one new heart,
I didn't deserve another one.
Justin, you don't have to feel
guilty about having a new heart.
God wants you to live.
That's why He sent you the heart.
I'm not stupid.
God didn't send me the heart.
- There's no such thing as God.
- Justin!
Marion. Marion, it's all right.
The heart I have now, my mom told me
the heart came from Santa.
I thought elves made it in their factory
or whatever.
- But that's not true, is it?
- No, it isn't.
Yeah.
Because I heard the nurses talking.
Where it really came from
is some other kid.
Some other kid had to die
so I could live.
Justin.
Baby.
And then I outgrew that kid's heart.
So, for the last two years,
my mom has been praying
that another kid would die for me.
That's what you pray for all the time.
Isn't it, Mom?
That's what she prayed for, Father.
- How does God feel about that?
- Justin...
Justin...
Justin, baby. Wake up, Justin.
Nurse!
- Oh, please, no, no...
- Move, please.
- Code blue! Just stay back.
- Justin!
Justin, baby, I'm right here.
I love you.
Please, just shut her up.
He's in V-Fib.
Charge the paddles to 100.
- Charge.
- Clear.
Clear.
Can you get him back on the list?
If it's a bad heart...
- It's not a bad heart.
- Can you get him back on the list?
He's waited two years for this heart.
He has to fight for it,
decide he wants to live.
Medically speaking,
is there anything we haven't done?
The way you're feeling right now,
it's why I have to believe
in something bigger than me.
Because if I didn't,
that powerlessness would eat me alive.
- Drill, please.
- Any danger with two
- craniotomies in one day?
- No more than with one.
- Is there any music?
- Any requests?
Christmas carols... or Hanukkah.
Is there such a thing as
Hanukkah carols?
The brain is a mysterious thing,
Dr. Stevens.
You never know
what may penetrate the psyche.
- Look!
- Kissing ulcers.
One's perfed, the other one's bleeding.
Two ulcers.
I'm not surprised, with that family.
I should have thrown them out.
Why didn't I?
That's what I should have done.
Stop whining, O'Malley.
You had your chance, you didn't take it.
Right. Sorry.
- Do not kick me.
- Excuse me?
Are you kicking me under the table,
O'Malley?
No!
Then clearly, I wasn't talking to you.
You cannot kick me
while I am doing my job.
Thank you.
Wake up.
No wonder you failed. Do you expect
to learn this stuff by osmosis?
What are you doing here?
I'm a farmer, OK? I've been
drooling, puking, and crapping my pants.
You came here to help me study?
Well, I'm not actually
crapping my pants now, am I?
Why would you want to help me
after what I did?
Because it's what Jesus
would freaking do!
You know,
I don't believe in Santa either, Justin.
Or God.
I believe in medicine.
And it's a medical miracle you're alive.
With the heart you had, you should have
died two weeks after you were born.
Except some surgeon figured out a way
to give you someone else's heart,
which is so much cooler than Santa.
So, I'm just saying...
I think you should decide to live.
Live so you can become a doctor and you
can find a way to do heart transplants
without someone having to die.
Or, you know,
live so you can grow up and have kids.
And you know what?
Raise them not to believe in Santa.
Man, that would piss your mom off.
Just decide to live.
Because in your case,
dying really isn't the best revenge.
- How is she?
- She gonna be all right?
She lost a lot of blood, but we were
able to replace it and repair the tear.
She's going to require
several days' observation,
- but she should have a full recovery.
- Thank God.
"Thank God" is right, because we're
certainly not going to thank you.
We should sue you for all you're worth.
We sat here and sat here and sat here...
- You wanna help me out?
- Really?
You got your second chance,
just don't screw it up.
...three whole days for her operation.
I should sue you
and this whole damned hospital!
OK, yeah. You could sue us,
or you could consider the possibility
of just shutting the hell up.
- What did you say to me? Did you hear?
- I heard him.
- You can't talk to her like that.
- Where is my daughter?
- I'd like to see her.
- Well, you can't.
I am her doctor, she is my patient
this is a hospital,
the kind of place where people
generally need peace and quiet.
So, no. Right now, you can't see her.
I'm not saying this because
you threatened to sue Dr. Bailey
who spent hours saving your daughter's
life, saving your wife's life.
I'm saying this
because she is my patient,
and she is in the recovery wing
of this hospital trying to recover.
And visiting hours are over.
So, good night.
And merry Christmas.
Interns. Too emotional.
Apologies.
Uh...
Is the nausea constant or intermittent?
Constant.
When...
When did it first start?
After I worked in the fields all day.
Do you have any allergies
you're aware of?
No.
Izzie...
I never wanted to hurt you.
You didn't hurt me.
I don't even know you. I'm a farmer.
- You're still the patient?
- What does it look like?
It's organophosphates.
Pesticide poisoning.
Crying's a symptom. That's it, right?
Right.
Hey.
- Hey.
- You OK?
- You look...
- Yeah, yeah.
- You know. Holidays.
- Yeah.
I do know.
- Merry Christmas.
- Hey.
- Merry Christmas, Joe.
Merry Christmas.
Double scotch, single malt.
You're a good man.
Hey, Dr. Shepherd.
Dr. Shepherd.
So, how's Mr. Epstein's frontal lobe?
He woke up smiling.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
What are you drinking?
- It's hot buttered rum. It's delicious.
- It's Dickensian.
No. Well, yeah. It is Christmas.
Christmas, Derek. We love Christmas.
At least we used to.
Yeah. Christmas makes you want
to be with the people you love.
I'm not saying this to hurt you
or because I want to leave you,
because I don't.
Meredith wasn't a fling.
She wasn't revenge.
I fell in love with her.
That doesn't go away
because I decided to stay with you.
There's an old proverb that
says you can't choose your family.
You take what the fates hand you.
And like them or not, love them or not,
understand them or not...
Justin took a turn.
His fever's down and his BP's up.
I wonder what got through to him.
I don't know.
... you cope.
Pretty.
Yeah.
Then there's the school of thought
that says the family you're born into
is simply a starting point.
What are we doing?
Lights.
They feed you and clothe you
and take care of you
until you're ready
to go into the world...
and find your tribe.
www.tvsubtitles.net