prevously on "grey's anatomy...
i'm george.
we met at the mixer
you had on a black dress
strappy sandalsand a slit up the side.
i've had this thing for
my roommate since, like, day one.
she's pretty great,you know?
who's thatch?
my dad.
thatcher.
she never talks about him.
i'm glad you moved in.
oh, so she moved in with you.
didn't she tell you?
and what i know now is that
when i go into my bedroom,
i'm gonna see that my wife
is cheating on me with mark
who happened to be my best friend.
after careful consideration
and many sleepless nights
(here's what i've decided)
there's no such thing as a grown-up.
we move on. we move out
we move away from our families
and form our own
oh, no
hello?
no. dr. burke.
yes.
yes, i'll let her know.
that was your landlord.
he wants you to know
that there's a minor flood
in your apartment.
your other apartment.
but the basic insecurities
the basic fears
and all those old wounds
just grow up with us
i'm exhausted.
me, too.
and just when we think
that life and circumstance
(have forced us to truly)
once and for all become an adult...
i was going at it all night
in the on call room.
what's your excuse?
your mother says something like that
mom.
i tell you, that man
makes me purr like a kitten.
mom.
when he isn't making me
growl like a tiger.
stop.
and my husband wonders
why i'm not interested
in him anymore.
or worse,something like that
if he had any balls at all,
he would leave on his own.
no. he plays stupid.
he's waiting for me to kick him out.
i come home with a hickey
on my shoulder
a hickey, for god's sake
like i'm some sex-crazed teenager,
which, let's face it,these days, i am,
and what does thatcher do?
pretends he doesn't see it.
we get bigger
we get taller
we get older
but... for the most part
we're still a bunch of kids
running around the playground
trying desperately to fit in
you know, he's acting like
i committed a crime,
like my apartment is full of stolen goods.
he's acting like i kept my apartment
to hide stolen goods
so i could do
illegal transplants for money.
are you sure he's not
just acting like you lied
about moving in?
okay,what's wrong with you?
my mommy's a filthy whore.
you have dirty in your eyes.
i'm not doing dirty with you anymore.
it was a one-time lapse in judgment.
well, it was a 4-time lapse in judgment.
well, it's not gonna happen again.
oh. okay.
i'm serious.
we're friends,and it didn't work
when we tried to be more than that.
so...
as fun as it was,
it's not gonna happen again.
stop looking at me.
i'm not looking at you,
i'm rounding.
i'm rounding, too.
-fine.
chuck eaton, 54,
has stage 3b non-small cell
lung cancer
with possible invasion of the pleura
and a history of c.o.p.d.
he's had extensive
chemo-radiotherapy
with minimal regression of the tumor.
he's been admitted
for radical en bloc resection.
i was a smoker.
the, uh, oncologist...
he explained that i have a 25% chance
of surviving the, uh, surgery.
well, unfortunately,that's about right.
if you should elect not to proceed,
we can make you more comfortable.
with all due respect, uh...
there's no way
that you can make a man
dying a slow death comfortable.
i'll roll the dice.
how do i look today?
would you say, you know,
i look nice?
you could usea little more lip gloss,
but, yes,
you're very pretty.
aw, you're mean.
i'm just kidding. you look fine.
seriously, how's my breath?
george.
would you just talk to her?
who?
what?
good morning, dr. bailey.
hello, baby.
are the o.r.'s up and running?
uh, yeah,they're fully functional.
uh, except there's some
smoke damage to the corridors.
how about you?
you fully functional?
i'm fine.
how's your husband?
taking him home tomorrow.
yes, we are. yes. yes...
okay,this is not a tea party.
go. work. save some lives.
now!
do it now.
jake burton, 15, has advanced
craniodiaphyseal dysplasia.
was admitted last night
after complaining of headaches.
and he's not a complainer.
he's been havingsome nausea as well.
really, okay?
may i, please?
jake, can i get you to sit up, please?
sure.
all right, okay.
now i want you to look
right here for me. thank you.
you know, if you pretend
i'm a lion, it helps.
sorry?
if you pretend i'm a lion
instead of a really messed up kid,
you get a talking circus animal,
which is way easier to look at.
dr. yang, what's our
immediate concern?
uh, that the bony tumors
are growing inward
and encroaching on his brain.
"invasive non-small cell
with a history of c.o.p.d."?
guy's pretty much a goner, huh?
sensitivity...i like that in a stranger.
are you new here?
visiting.
confounded by all the rain,
and it's only
my first day in town.
you get used to it.
makes me want
to stay in bed all day.
we just met, and already
you're talking about bed.
not very subtle.
subtle's never been my strong suit.
so...
do you ever go out with co-workers?:
i, um, make it a rule not to.
then i am so glad that i don't work here.
are you hitting on me
in a hospital?
would that be wrong?
meredith.
ow. ah.
what the hell was that?
that was mark.
punching out people
on my surgical floor?
my head of neurosurgery
punching out people
on my surgical floor?
put the ice back on your hand, derek.
my hand is fine.
put the damn ice on
your $2-million-a-year hand.
now... would someone tell me
what the hell happened?
that was mark.
who's mark?
he and derek used to work together
back in new york.
and, uh...
they were...we were all close friends
until...
derek found us in bed together.
you put your weight behind it?
yes, sir.
well, all right, then.
what the hell is he doing here?
i have no idea.
derek and i always did have
the same taste in women.
excuse me?
you're derek's lusty intern, right?
i heard about you
all the way back in new york.
you're famous.
well...
i heard about you
all the way here in seattle,
so i guess we have a lot in common.
we're the dirty mistresses.
i suppose we are.
my $400-an-hour shrink
says that
it's because behind this rugged
and confident exterior
i'm self-destructive and self-loathing
to an almost pathological degree.
hey, we do have a lot in common.
you know, it's funny.
der...
derek walks in on me
naked with his wife
actually in the throes
and he just turns around
and walks away.
but he sees me
so much as talking to you
and i'm on the ground bleeding.
interesting, don't you think?
what do you think you're doing?
you need stitches.
i know. hold the mirror.
why is he suturing his own face?
to turn me on.
because he's mark sloan.
he's like the go-to plastic surgeon
on the east coast.
that's the guy
addison was sleeping with?
well, you can't really
blame her, can you?
no, not really.
yes, you can.
mcsexy wants an x-ray
to check for fractures,
and i think it's a bad idea if i take him.
why? why?
i'm on it. why is it a bad idea?
mcsexy?
no?
mm. mcyummy.
-no
-no.
mcsteamy.
ah, there it is.
yep.
oh, excuse me,
i'm just chokin' back some mcvomit.
ooh.
i saw her first.
the night she met shepherd,
i had her ear.
we talked,
and i can't even remember what i said.
you know when you haven't
had sex for awhile,
you sort of forget how good it is
and don't really need it much?
yeah, that doesn't happen to guys.
it's like a beas...
a beast that was asleep
for a long,long time.
and now the beast is wide awake
and wants to be fed,
and the food that alex gave it was...
it was
good food, george.
something needs to be done
about your taste.
ah! you're just jealous
because you're beast is still asleep.
eh, my beast isn't asleep.
my beast never sleeps.
mr. eaton.
do you need a hand with that?
um, if you could set up the tripod,
that would be very helpful.
are you...
what are you doing?
i'm dying, dear.
one in four...
i, uh, i've never done well
with odds like that.
some...some people are lucky.
i just never have been.
the camera's for posterity,
for saying good-bye.
do you want me to hold
the camera for you?
you're very kind.thank you.
okay, we're recording.
this...this is a message
for suzie zelman
my...my college sweetheart
and...and the love of my life.
suzie...
i loved you with my whole heart...
and i never would've
stopped loving you
if you hadn't been the vile whore
to ever walk the planet earth.
you deserve that...
that drunken imbecile
that you slept with and then married.
and when, at the reunion,
i..i met your ugly children
i knew you had done me a real favor.
i am so deeply happy
that i'll never have to see
your face again.
love, chuck.
would you please, uh,
put in a fresh tape, dear?
what about that
jaw reconstruction you did
using a microvascular
free transfer from the foot?
you interested in plastics?
absolutely.
you might want to consider a transfer
to new york or los angeles.
you're not gonna see
any heat up here.
well, actually...
you ever seen an advanced case
of craniodiaphyseal dysplasia?
lionitis?
restrained driver
in a minor m.v.c.
vitals are stable,but witnesses saw
seizure activity behind the wheel.
i really don't think i need to be here.
you should really let us
determine that, ma'am.
witnesses said she was
screaming, shuddering
and--and clamping her jaw.
do you have a seizure disorder
that you're aware of?
epilepsy?
it's not epilepsy.i don't have any
oh, no. oh, god.
it's happening again.
oh, no.
was that a...
did she just have a...
orgasm.
spontaneous orgasms.
are you sure?
kinda ha to miss.
ms. calva,
i'm dr. montgomery-shepherd.
it's pamela.
since we're gonna be
talking about... you know,
may as well get familiar.
okay, pamela,
can you tell me
how long this has
been happening to you?
for a few months,
i guess.
how often?
about, i don't know,
seven or eight times a day.
every day?
uh, dr. stevens.
i'm sorry.
every day?
yes, every day.
and you haven't seen
a doctor about this before?
it not exactly something
you want to cure, is it?
dr. o'malley
sorry.
mum...is it?
i went to my doctor.
he sent me to a shrink.
and he didn't do any tests?
pammy,you back here?
oh, god, no.
you called my father?
he's your emergency contact person.
pammy, what happened?
you were in an accident?
i caused the accident, d.
you had one of your...
episodes. yeah.
oh, no.
damn it.
she's a junior at u-dub.
she's a math major.
the last three semesters,
she made the honor roll.
high up in the honor roll.
mr. calva, we're gonna...
run some tests
and we're gonna...
we're gonna figure out what's
causing your daughter's...
episodes.
this right, episodes.
okay.
and when you were 14,
you stole laura brendese
right out from under me.
you knew how i felt about her.
don't say you didn't know
because you knew.
and you went for her anyway.
what kind of human being
does that to his little brother?
he was 14. cut him some slack
for god's sakes.
oh, i'm sorry.
i forgot we were recording.
if you wouldn't mind just rewinding
a little bit, please?
i'm a doctor, not a videographer.
and i do need to prep you for surgery.
but you offered to help.
when i thought
you were saying good-bye.
i am saying good-bye.
none of these people not one of them
knows how i really feel.
my whole life,
i've kept it all inside.
i-i don't want to carry this
with me to my grave.
you seem like such a nice man.
wouldn't you just rather
you remember you that way?
no.
please rewind the tape.
okay, jake
it can get a little cramped in there,
so you have to try not to move.
yeah, uh, this is, like,
my 50th m.r.i. experience.
right, sorry.
it's okay.
you have really nice eyes,
you know?
well, i'm just sayin' that
you're mostly all...
all surly and hard core,
but your eyes aren't.
i'm really big on eyes.
they're the only part of my face
where tumors aren't growing.
yeah, you've got nice eyes.
yeah?
mm-hmm.
you..you get that...
that i'm jailbait, right?
meredith.
chief.
chief
can i ask you something
not work-related?
okay.
do you remember my father?
of course.
do you know why he left?
i believe your mother asked him to.
right, but do you know why?
no.
no, i'm sorry. i don't.
well...
have a good day.
thanks. you, too.
dr. yang, book an o.r.please
how--how is that possible?
it's precision work.
it won't be easy, but--
dr. sloan, can i help you
with something?
he says he can fix my face.
he says he can make me
look like normal.
what did he say?
did you hear that?
did he call him a crack whore?
-why would he call him a crack whore?
-oh, shut up.
i'm trying to read lips.
look, shepherd's gesturing.
big gesturing.
what do you got?
shepherd and sloan battling it out.
oh, it's gettin' good.
why, what do you got?
just a woman down in the e.r...
having spontaneous orgasms.
wait, wait, wait. wait.
that is not the point.
the point is the kid wants his
face fixed and i want to do it.
the point is,
you wanna get published!
well, yeah.
and i'm guessing your chief
of surgery does, too.
you know how the press loves
a good before and after shot,
richard.
call me dr. webber.
derek,
out of friendship to you,
i would very much love
to say no to this jackass.
but as chief--
please don't say it.
dr. sloan, if you can get the parents
to sign a consent form...
round two goes to the jackass.
which one? which one?
oh, god. oh, no.
oh, no.
oh, it's happening.
doctors,there something you need?
well, in that case,move on.
no, no
anyone get what mcdreamy
or mcsteamy sees in her?
she's mchot.
mcyeah, she is.
oh, come on.
you're not even
a little bit happy to see me?
go home. whatever it is
you came here to do,
just drop it and leave.
hey, we all made mistakes,
addison, all three of us...
mark...
but somehow...somehow,
i lost my best friend
and the woman i loved.
please... don't say that.
he doesn't know how we felt.
he doesn't know you stayed
with me after he left.
how do you expect
to work out a marriage
if you can't even
be honest with him?
why are you here?
for one reason...
to bring you home.
i miss you, addison.
i'm in love with my husband, mark.
but he's not in love with you.
he's in love with that intern,
and he's not even trying to hide it.
now why would you want
to stick around for that?
i think you're making it up.
i'm not.
-i saw it four times.
-what?
a woman with spontaneous orgasms.
really
you're just jealous 'cause
you didn't see it yourself.
oh, i totally am.
spontaneous orgasms, really?
you look really nice today.
any chance they're contagious?
spontaneous orgasms.
it's that would solve so many problems.
it would. it would.
i think you smell nice, too.
you know, it's like,
you see someone throw up,
it makes you want to throw up too.
kinda like that?
kinda like.
you know what? i'm not hungry.
do you hear me?
i'm not hungry.
neither is the beast.
"the beast"...is that, like,
some sly reference to your penis?
get your mind out of
the gutter, crack whore.
no, it's not alex's penis.
it's...you know
when you haven't had
sex for a long time
and you forget how good it is,
and so you want it less?
yeah, that doesn't happen to me.
me either.
i grew my hair for her,and...
i know.
i don't even think she's noticed.
you could just try
telling her how you feel.
um, guys?
she's moving,
like, a lot.
pamela,
you have to hold still.
okay.
that's not helping the beast sleep, is it?
no.
no, it's not.
you're drawing the medial to the tumor.
-yeah,
-it's a guideline
for what the bone structure should be.
hear that?
i'm gonna have bone structure.
jake...
so what do you think,am i a dal?
or more of a picasso?
could you stop doing that
for a minute, please?
jake...
jake... i'm sorry.
this surgery,the brain surgery,
is very dangerous.
no, don't say that.
y-you don't get to change your mind.
you know, i know dr. sloan
has made you some big promises,
but the bony tumors
inside your skull are bad.
i don't care.
the bleeding will be hard to control.
i'm not trying to frighten you,
-i just want you to under--
-i do understand.
i understand
that this has nothing to do
with the plastic surgery.
so if i'm gonna be under
the knife anyway, then--
-the plastic surgery could--
-sorry to interrupt--
what you need to understand--
excuse me.
jakes actually right.
no reason to put him through
a second surgery
and a second round of anesthesia.
it's much safer just to
do it all at once.
honey, we just want to focus
on keeping you alive.
mom, i-i almost died
when i was 10 years old.
and then again when i was 12.
and then again last year.
but...but
but i'm still alive.
i'm still alive,
so i say we go for it.
jake...
look, i know that you think
i'm perfect just the way i am--
but that's your job to do that.
but... for once in my life,
i'd like to think
that someone else thought that.
please.
you've given up surgery
to go into clerical work?
i'm fulfilling a patient's dying wish
by sending hate mail
to everyone he's ever met.
yeah,
right now i understand the impulse.
me, too.
why do people cheat?
that's a good question.
why do you think she cheated on you?
were you different then?
were you a bad husband?
i was, uh...
oh, i was just a little...absent.
not that that's an excuse for her.
do you think things
would've been different
if you'd had kids?
do i think
she wouldn't have cheated?
i don't know.
all right, man, jake's ready to roll.
i'm sorry.
did i interrupt something?
no. it's fine.
pamela,
you should really try and relax.
i am trying to relax.
the episodes happen
when i don't relax.
do you really think you can fix this?
i, uh, i hate to be insensitive, but...
would it be the worst thing
ever if we can't?
i mean...
you know, i like sex
as much as the next girl,
like in bed
or even in private.
but when you can't go to the movies
or drive a car
or go to church with your parents...
oh, my god.
you know that dream
where you show up at high school
and you're naked?
yeah.
yeah, well, i would really,
really like to wake up.
it's crossed
the intrathoracic fascia?
i'm afraid so.
i'm gonna have to go into the chest wall.
he made 17 hate tapes.
i'm sorry?
videotapes of himself
telling people how much he hated them
spewing every hurt feeling he ever had.
and he mailed them?
no.
he wanted me to, but i don't
think it's a good idea.
he was scared.
he was in shock.
he wasn't thinking clearly.
that's not for you to decide, dr. grey.
he asked you for something,
and you told him you would do it.
if you don't,
that doesn't make you noble.
it makes you a liar.
did you know she kept her artment?
yeah.i did. sorry.
and now...
dr. shepherd
-is opening the skull-cap.
-is it harder to get
-through the bony tumors?
-that's what he's doin'.
yes, he is.
basin.this idone.
cottonoid.
give me the sponge.
oh, son of a bitch
all right
hang another unit of blood.
oh i got
somebody change that bag of blood, please.
that's too much blood.
put it in the pressure infuser.
no carotid.
we've got v-fib.
start c.p.r. and bag him.
paddles.get the paddles.
he's losing a lot of blood.
someone get f.f.p.
charge to 200.
charging.
clear.
shame he never had his face fixed.
dr. sloan.
yeah.
all right.
i got the parents' approval.
you don't...really need those.
oh, right.
scalpel.
mr. eaton,
can you hear me?
oh, god.
no, no, don't try to sit up.
you're gonna be in pain for some time.
but i'm pleased to report
that we removed the entire tumor.
wait, i'm--i'm alive?
yes, sir.
you are alive.
my--my tapes?
would you like me
to throw them away?
no.
i'd like you to mail them.
i-i have to say my piece.
sometimes a man has to say his piece.
mer... uh, do you want--
uh, i want to take you
out for a drink tonight.
and not--maybe not joe's.
maybe someplace where we can talk.
yeah, there's something i need..i want...
to talk to you about.
it's important.
it's...
i don't want to make videotapes
on my deathbed, george.
she had an affarie
y-yes.
why didn't you stay and fight for us?
i did. i...i tried.
why didn't you try harder?
you just left.
meredith...
is there anything that you need?
a...anything at all?
no.
i don't need anything from you.
hey.
i haven't see you all day.
i didn't want to see you today.
it's not my fault he showed up, derek.
i know.
don't beat yourself up--
i'm gonna take the stairs.
oh, come on.derek.
how come you can
forgive her but not me?
i didn't forgive her, and with you
i have no obligation to try.
your marriage is over,addison.
all you have to do is admit it.
then you can come back home with me.
i'm goin' to the bar across the street.
meet me there.
he looks...
peaceful.
he does.
i am preston burke,
a widely-renowned
cardiothoracic surgeon.
i am... a professional.
and more than that,
i am a good and kind person.
i am person that cleans up
behind myself.
i am a person that cooks well.
and you...you are
an unbelievable slob.
a slovenly, angry intern.
i am preston burke.
and you...you are the most competitive
most guarded, most stubborn
most challenging person
i have ever met.
and i love you.
what the hell is the matter with you
that you won't just let me?
i gave up my apartment 20 minutes ago.
well, all right, then.
i've heard that it's possible to grow up.
i've just never met anyone
who's actually done it
dr. stevens,
after the surgery,
will i still be able to...
when i want to, will i
still be able to have...
you know...
episodes?
even better, pamela...
you'll be able to have orgasms.
without parents to defy
we break the rules
we make for ourselves...
we throw tantrums
when things don't go our way...
hey.
she doesn't hear me.
what?
she doesn't even hear me when i talk.
she will if you make her.
you fed the beast, didn't you?
twice.
i'll see you later.
bye.
we whisper secrets
withour friends in the dark...
meredith came to saw me today.
hmm. poor baby.
poor thing.
her father left, you know?
i think she knows about us, ellis.
i think she's figured it out.
she's 5 years old,richard.
we look for comfort
where we can find it...
this seat taken?
i guess not.
double scotch,
single malt.
you look sad.
i just saw my father
for the first time in 20 years.
how'd that go?
it coulda gone better.
what are you still doing here?
i'm hoping addison shows up.
you're still in love with her?
you're still in love with him.
she won't show, you know?
no?
he's not the kind of guy
you leave if you can help it.
what if you're wrong?
what if, just this once,
life comes down on the side
of the dirty mistresses?
and we hope...
against all logic
against all experience.
like children...
we never give up hope.
come in.
i know i'm not
a world-renowned surgeon.
and i know i'm not a lot of things
that you've gone for in the past.
i know.
but...
i would never leave you.
i would never hurt you.
and i will never stop loving you.
www.tvsubtitles.net