Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- What will happen when she's on leave?
- A new resident?
My mother is very sick. I'm the
only person she'll allow to see her.
Cujo has to go!
Hey, Doc. Buddy.
- Thanks for doing this.
- He'll be fine.
I grew up in a trailer park. Paid for
med school by posing in my underwear.
I walk into the OR
and everyone hopes I'm the nurse.
The nurses are overworked.
Sorry, we're short-staffed.
Unhappy nurses lead to...
I don't even want to think about it.
We go on strike in ten days.
In surgery,
there's a red line on the floor
that marks the point where the hospital
goes from being accessible
to being off-limits
to all but a special few.
Crossing the line unauthorized
is not tolerated.
Fair hours, fair wages!
Can't cross
the picket line. I can't.
I don't like it, George,
but what choice do we have?
You took an oath to heal.
You're a healer.
Dad's a truck driver, Mom's a teacher.
The news shows me crossing this line?
They'll outlive me
just to pee on my grave.
In general,
lines are there for a reason.
Has there been any blood yet?
I heard they brought in scab nurses.
For safety. For security.
For clarity.
I think the nurses would know
we are on their side. Don't they?
We're doctors. We have sick patients
inside! I mean, we have surgeries.
OK.
Then you go first.
- Don't cross! Scabs!
- Screw it.
Fair hours! Fair wages!
Yeah, doing my job.
Doing my job. Ha-ha!
They threw food at her!
That is just wrong!
Fine. I'm going in.
- Change your own bedpans, Stevens!
- Enjoy your syphilis, Olivia!
- George, are you coming?
- No, I'm good here.
If you choose to cross
the line, you do so at your own risk.
- Good morning.
- Morning, Meredith!
- How is she today?
- She's great.
She really lights up
when Dr. Webber visits.
And I did not back down.
Not in my OR,
not in front of those jock Ortho idiots.
It was the last time Windsor called you
"little lady." Even behind your back.
One day, I'll be Chief of Surgery.
The first woman Chief. You watch.
I don't doubt it.
So why is it...
Don't doubt for a minute.
... that the bigger the line,
the greater the temptation to cross it?
Fair hours, fair wages!
And I can't say this enough.
Charts are organized by room number.
I know you're temps,
but there's no excuse for sloppiness.
- Where's Edmonds' chart?
- I need vitals.
Know why I stopped being a nurse?
Doctors.
Doctors who don't know
how to pitch in.
Right.
This place is going to hell.
We need the real nurses.
We need 40 nurses to relieve the
overtime that they're striking about.
That's $2 million a year we don't have.
Have you checked under the couch?
I always find spare change there.
OK, I'm silencing myself.
That's him.
He's published twice and he's flawless.
He's a freak.
He doesn't let you speak in the OR.
- Yeah, but he's flawless.
- I think it is him. What's his name?
Oh, yeah. Mouth breather guy.
But he'll let you do a procedure
on your own if he likes you.
- What are we doing?
- Figuring out who'll replace Bailey.
Yang! Stevens! Grey! O'Malley! Karev!
Here you are!
I was looking for you guys in
the locker room, but you weren't there.
Then I thought, "Maybe my interns
are looking for me too."
Then I come out here and here you are.
Yeah! You guys look like a great group!
Awesome. My horoscope said it was
going to be a very challenging day,
and I was a little worried.
But, no. You guys...
Yeah, you look like a good group.
Which is great because we are going to
have so much fun. Hi! Hi, first of all.
Ow. Ow.
- Sorry. Am I hurting you?
- No, you're touching me.
I'm Sydney Heron. Fourth year.
My philosophy, just so you know,
is, um, is heal with love.
OK? So, wonderful.
So, Alex, Izzie, Meredith, Cristina.
Our group is just missing...
O'Malley. He's cowering
behind the strike line like a girl.
Standing up for what he believes in,
that's my kind of girl. Right?
The ER needs somebody down there
for a consult.
- Does anybody... Who wants to...
- We get to pick?
- Me! I'm on it!
- I'll help.
I have patients I need to check on.
So it looks like just you and me,
Izzie McGee.
All right. It's Stevens.
Izzie Stevens.
Oh, no. I knew!
I was just rhyming.
Oh. Rhyming. Right.
Yeah, that's neat.
- Dr. Stevens?
- Yeah.
- Can I use you on a consult?
- OK, I'm on it! Absolutely.
Yeah.
- You need a consult for a rash?
- It's spreading pretty fast.
I wanted to be sure
there's nothing surgical.
Mrs. Solomon? Oh!
Sorry.
- We're on our honeymoon.
- Yeah.
Sweet.
Can you, um...
...dismount, please?
- Yeah.
- OK, great.
Ah!
Len! Lenny.
Is that you?
Lenny.
Are you OK, ma'am?
"Grace Bickham." Mrs. Bickham,
do you know who your doctor is?
- Len?
- I don't see your chart here.
- Are you there?
- I need you to calm down for me, OK?
- Lenny?
- Is that your husband?
Where is he?
He was here.
I'm sure he'll be back any moment.
You're having trouble breathing.
I need to run some tests.
- Lenny.
- Nurse? I need a nurse in here!
Fair hours, fair wages!
You can go, George.
We won't throw donuts.
- I can take the donuts.
- Then what are you doing here?
Teachers' strike of '03?
Mom walked the line for 48 days.
I can't... just... I can't cross.
- So go home.
- I can't go home.
You don't just go...
Yeah, and get kicked out of the program.
Lose my place as a resident.
I'm a doctor. Don't do...
Don't... Don't...
I'm a union guy.
- So that means?
- Give me that sign.
- All right!
- Whoo!
All right, Dr. O'Malley!
Help! I need a nurse in here.
Her pressure's falling.
- She stopped breathing.
- Whoa. Is she dying?
- Are you a nurse?
- I'm, like, a nursing student.
I need to intubate.
Get a 7.5 tube.
They're out in the hall.
Not that one.
The one that says 7-5.
- I'm in.
- Awesome.
Is that too much?
It's a lot of extra amniotic fluid,
Cheyenne, but your baby looks strong.
Does that mean we can go?
I mean, I appreciate you seeing us,
but this is a long drive for us and
I can't afford to miss another shift.
Unfortunately, Ms. Wood,
the mass on the baby's neck
is what's causing
the build-up of fluid.
It's also obstructing
her airway and the spine.
- Mom?
- It's all right. Let's listen.
We're gonna do a procedure
called an EXIT surgery.
We do a C-Section
and half deliver the baby.
Half deliver?
We pull the head and arms out,
but we don't cut the umbilical cord.
Why?
The tumor won't let air
get to the baby's lungs.
We need the umbilical cord
to keep her alive during the operation.
It's cool, if you think about it.
You'll be your baby's
life support machine.
After the surgery, if all goes well,
we cut the umbilical cord
and you'll be the mother
of a healthy baby girl.
- How's that sound?
- It sounds expensive.
Well, your doctor at the clinic
is a former student of mine.
So... it's covered.
I'm going to go ahead
and take this up to the lab.
The hospital gets a write-off, and
it makes Dr. Shepherd look good, so...
- So it's not charity?
- It's not charity.
- What time's your shift?
- 6:00 to 6:00.
- Graveyard. In Chehalis?
- Yeah.
That's three hours away.
You better get going.
I'll look out for her.
Incoming temp nurses
to conference room three.
- Chief.
- Hello, Meredith.
Saw my mother this morning.
Did you?
How is she?
She's fine.
I'm glad to hear it.
Give her my best.
Why are you...?
It's to mark the borders
of the infection.
We'll watch it.
If it doesn't cross the line,
- you'll get IV antibiotics.
- If it does cross the line?
It'd mean the infection's aggressive.
We'd have to do a muscle biopsy.
- You'd take out a piece of my muscle?
- Mm-hm.
- We're supposed to run a 10K tomorrow.
- Oh, on this leg? I doubt it.
Can you tell us when
you noticed the rash?
When we were
climbing Rainier yesterday.
Wow! You go up
the Emmons Glacier route?
Please. You can do that in an SUV.
We did Liberty Ridge.
Oh, wow. That's hardcore.
Hi, I'm Sydney Heron.
These guys' teacher.
I'm Claire, this is Wade.
It's our honeymoon.
Wow, that's amazing.
God, look at that rock.
Did you sustain any trauma on the hike?
Did you fall down or bang your leg?
- No.
- Well, she cut her foot
on oyster shells
at the beach a couple days ago.
- We were windsurfing in Puget Sound.
- Oh, wow.
You need a honeymoon
to recover from your honeymoon.
- Ow.
- Right?
My leg's going to be OK, right?
Yeah. It's probably
a simple skin infection.
Uh, no, it's not. Look.
- Hey.
- Your dog's fine.
- He's your dog now.
I miss him.
He misses you too.
You should come visit.
The dog, I mean.
I'm walking away now.
So I'm looking for a neurosurgeon
to consult on a fetal spinal tumor.
Do you know anybody good?
- Fair hours, fair wages!
- Don't ask George.
- I'm not. He's a doctor.
- Go ahead. Just ask him.
I'm showing support.
They whisper and point.
- George?
- What?
- We need a favor.
- Ava Jenkins in peds, room 4114.
It's time to change her dressing
and it's scary for her
but if you sing the alphabet
or the Wheels on the Bus song
- she can handle it.
- Ms. O'Brien from 2412?
She'll have a panic attack if they don't
check on her once an hour.
- And there's this guy in 2924...
- Hang on. Hang on.
You want me to cross the picket line?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Because they're
our patients too, George.
And we can't.
- Anyone care to probe the wound?
- I do.
I'd like to try your
"healing with love".
I like the way you think, Alex.
You do the honors.
Cristina, it looks like someone
needs to learn how to share.
Now slide it in.
- Whoa. No resistance.
- Let me see.
- Dr. Heron?
Yes?
No healthy muscle
gives way that easily.
My god. Oh, this poor girl. OK everyone,
we're locking down the OR.
All nonessential personnel
must leave now.
- Was that Pathology?
- It's necrotizing fasciitis.
- The flesh-eating bacteria?
- In the flesh.
Oh, good. Somebody's in here.
How's she doing?
- You intubated her?
- Yeah?
- You intubated her.
- I had to.
She was struggling.
Her sats were in the 80's.
She was in a room all alone.
What?
A temp nurse found the paperwork
from her chart on the second floor.
- And...
- You put a tube in Grace.
- She put a tube in Grace?
Mrs. Bickham was diagnosed
with end stage COPD.
- She's on hospice.
- End of life care?
DNR.
Do not resuscitate.
You schnook!
You were supposed to let her die.
No machines, she said.
She did. I remember.
Her daughter Alice was there
with her girlfriend.
Uh, she's a lesbian.
The daughter. Nice girls.
Stop with the rambling, Agnes.
Make your point.
I'm sorry.
Who are you, exactly?
Mrs. Bickham's sisters?
Oh, no. No.
Her sister Rose died in '83.
- May she rest in peace.
- Influenza. Or croup.
Only babies die of croup.
Rose died with a cold in her chest.
- Pneumonia.
- Right, pneumonia.
There was her other sister... Harriet.
May she rest in peace.
They cremated her.
Gracie wanted to die.
She made us all promise.
This really is something that
I need to speak with her husband about.
Lenny never talked much
when he was alive.
- Good luck getting a word now.
- Lenny's dead?
- May he rest in peace.
- But Grace said she just saw him.
Because she was trying
to cross over!
She almost died twice in the last month.
Said she saw him each time.
You ask me,
that's a little meshugena.
It's not meshugena!
He was waiting for her in the light.
Mm-hm. Which thanks to you,
she can't reach now.
- I need you to round all those 21 's...
- I'm not here.
- Excuse me?
- I'm here, but I'm not here.
- You won't be anywhere in 30 seconds...
- Sir, all due respect...
No offense intended, uh,
but I won't cross the picket line.
And yet you're standing in front of me.
The nurses want me to check
on their patients,
but then I'm going
right back out there.
- You're a doctor.
- Yes, sir.
But I'm also a union man.
All due respect.
There's no offense intended.
Fine.
Sir? While I have you here,
I'm supposed to tell you that
Mrs. O'Brien in 2412
is allergic to chocolate,
but she pulls the allergy sticker
off her chart.
- Wonderful.
- And that Mr...
...you're supposed to watch Mr. Roberts
in 2119 swallow his diuretics.
Apparently, he likes to hoard them.
Is that it?
Forty to 50 hours
of mandatory overtime is...
Yes, sir! I'm very sorry.
There's no offense intended.
What... wait, flesh-eating...
This is some kind of joke, right?
- She put you up to this?
- No. We have to amputate the leg.
- Cristina.
- We're on our honeymoon.
I'm sorry, Wade.
I know this is scary.
- Amputation is not the only option.
- It's the only sane...
If we don't get this
under control immediately,
- she is going to die.
- But there's another option?
We can try to save the leg
by cutting out the infection.
We might be able
to keep it functional.
- Gold star for Dr. Karev.
- I need to see her.
- No time.
- If we take her out of anesthesia
and put her back under...
You need to make a decision now.
I mean, she runs marathons.
This is our adventure honeymoon.
It's... I mean, it's who she is.
OK. Then we'll do everything
we can to save the leg.
You think this is a good idea?
I seriously think
this is a way cooler surgery.
Cheyenne, the prognosis is very good.
We want to go in and get as much
of the tumor out as possible
during your surgery.
- So my baby will be fine?
- Yes.
You may be able to take
her home this week.
- That soon?
- Absolutely. She'll be all yours.
- Oh. OK.
- OK.
If you or your mother have questions,
Dr. Stevens will page me.
See you later.
- Oh, Shakespeare.
- I was reading it to my baby.
It's really homework for English.
Was.
The baby wasn't due
for another few more weeks.
- And now I guess...
- No more school.
It's weird.
It's like when
you're in school... you hate it.
Until you can't go anymore.
- Have you made any plans?
- Plans?
Bought a crib, called about child care,
looked into assistance?
Not yet.
- You gonna live with your mom?
- I was supposed to be saving money
to get my own trailer home.
But I don't know.
I guess I just thought
I'd have more time.
Nine months goes by fast.
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
- I'll see you later.
- Bye.
So, Sydney, have you've seen
a lot of necrotizing fasciitis?
No. Have you?
- If the infection moves she'll die.
- If she wakes up without her leg,
- she might wish she had.
- Right.
She's young, healthy, a newlywed.
And your treatment plan
is based on... cuteness?
If she were an 80-year-old man,
you'd amputate.
She's not 80.
Where's your compassion?
My compassion?
Trying to save a patient from death
is compassionate.
I must say, I'm disappointed in you.
Why can't you be more like Alex?
Excuse me?
This guy, he's compassionate.
He's warm.
He's fighting
to save Claire's leg.
- We're going to win that fight.
- Yes.
Uh, excuse me. Restroom.
Burke.
- Hey. I thought you were in surgery.
- I was. Necrotizing fasciitis.
No kidding?
So why are you out here?
Because the new resident,
um, she's the new Bailey...
...except that she's the exact
opposite of Bailey
in absurd, horrifying,
profoundly disturbing ways.
I think the new resident
is killing our patient.
- Dr. Heron, is it?
- It is. And you are?
Preston Burke.
Dr. Burke. Wow, no kidding?
I'm a huge fan.
Thank you.
I, um...
I heard you had necrotizing fasciitis.
So we don't see
a lot of those around here.
Huh. Yeah, well. Being a cardiothoracic
surgeon, I wouldn't think you saw any.
Right. Well, uh...
I was curious what protocol
you were following here?
You were curious
or Cristina was concerned?
I hope you'll forgive the intrusion.
It's nothing personal.
It's just... we haven't
worked with you before.
And Dr. Yang wanted
to be sure that...
Dr. Yang wanted to be sure
the bimbo cheerleader
wasn't trying to kill a patient.
Am I right?
With all due respect,
I know you don't know me well,
but I'm pretty good at what I do.
My patient is a marathoner
and I told her husband
I'm going to try to save her leg.
So my plan...
...is to stand here
for as long as it takes
to scrape away every last cell
of necrotic flesh.
If it's still spreading,
we'll take the leg.
And if we do, then our eager
young intern here can hold the saw.
Now, unlike Dr. Karev, kindness
and compassion aren't very high
on her list of priorities,
but a little bone-saw action,
well, maybe that will earn me
some respect. Am I right?
Now, Dr. Yang,
you ready to scrub back in?
- You're the head of the whole hospital?
- Just the surgeons.
Well, they should make you
the head of everything.
She's batting the lashes.
You see this?
Dr. Webber, the point is,
Grace wants to be with her Lenny.
She misses him terribly.
You realize if I pull out the tube,
Grace will die?
We're old, magpie.
Not daft.
Pull the plug.
It's what she wants.
Ladies, I appreciate
your concern for your friend.
But we need to contact a durable
power of attorney to sign the release.
- That's Alice. Call Alice.
- Grace's daughter.
She's a lesbian.
Well, that's OK, isn't it?
I mean, she can still have
the power of attorney.
Uh, fine. But we'll need
Alice's signature.
- Good luck. She lives in Oregon.
- Oh, she can fax it.
I'm sorry.
We'll need her original signature.
Well, can't we just skip that part?
Bat the lashes again.
I think it was working.
Excuse me, ladies.
You're like the Old-Lady Whisperer.
They really cheer up
when you come around.
Meredith, you understand
if the daughter shows up tomorrow
and confirms she is DNR...
I have to kill my patient.
I know.
How you doing?
There something
I can do for you?
Oh, I'm fine, sir. I don't need
any help from you. Thank you.
"Sir, fare you well.
Hereafter, in a better world than this
I shall desire more love
and knowledge of you."
To Dr. O'Malley!
- O'Malley!
- Whoo!
She called me unkind.
Unkind and lacking in compassion.
In front of my boyfriend.
I am not unkind.
I think I have to
kill a woman tomorrow.
I have to take out the tube
that's keeping her alive.
Izzie.
This is the part where you
say what's wrong with you.
- Where're you going?
- I have to...
- I forgot something at work.
- We don't need her.
- I have to kill a woman tomorrow.
- And that's a problem why?
If it's what she wants,
it's what she wants.
And that is not unkind
or lacking in compassion.
I'm a very compassionate person.
- I'm more compassionate than Alex.
- Shut your pie hole, Yang.
Hey, Joe? Could we have
another round, please?
Yeah, give Nurse O'Malley
a drink on me.
What'd you say?
- Hey, uh, Karev just called me a nurse.
- At least nurses aren't butchers.
The worst thing you could come up with?
Was that an insult
or is that, uh...
was supposed to be funny?
Whoopsie.
Are you kidding me?
- I will kill you, you know that?
- Bring it on.
Bring..."Oh, bring it on."
OK, mama! Let's bring it on!
There's your squad.
Do you want to cheer it out, soccer mom?
- Are you going to throw down bedpans?
- Soccer mom?
Hey, hey, whoa, hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! If you beat each other up,
there won't be anybody left
to set your broken bones.
- Oh, that would be my job!
- Hey!
...studying my bones.
- We were just leaving.
- Yeah, I've got to go save lives.
Bye!
Excuse me.
They're my ride.
You're awake.
Hey. Yeah. Baby jumps up and down
on my belly all night,
makes me have to pee
all the time.
- You work long hours, huh?
- Yeah.
But I'm off work now. I...
I just came back to talk to you.
- I grew up in Chehalis too.
- Serious?
Serious.
Um, Forest Park.
- The trailer park up behind the church.
- On Route Six.
- My friend Shelley lives up there.
- My mom still lives there.
- No way.
- Yeah.
Can you keep a secret?
This is my daughter.
In the picture she's six,
but she's 11 now.
She lived in Santa Barbara,
but... they moved.
I don't know where.
But I know her name is Hannah.
- And she likes pigs.
- Pigs?
Yep. She collects them.
Like figurines and stuffed animals,
you know.
I think it's because
her mom read her Charlotte's Web.
I thought you were her mom.
I'm her mother.
But I'm not her mom.
Look...
I know that where we come from...
this kind of thing
doesn't get talked about.
But I wanted you to know
that there's more than one way
to be a good mother.
I wanted... I wanted better for her
than I could do at 16.
I love my baby.
Of course you do.
But you're reading her Shakespeare.
When you're working 12-hour shifts
at the diner, like our moms,
you won't be coming home
and reading her Shakespeare.
Oh. I could hear you
from six blocks away.
- Sorry.
- Don't be. I like it.
Um, I'm just not sure
how the neighbors would feel.
Which, by the way,
is not a thing
someone lacking in compassion
would be concerned with.
How's your patient's leg?
Carved all to hell,
but still on her body.
Oh, we're watching it overnight.
What's going on?
Never in my career have I questioned
a fellow surgeon in their OR.
I never understood
what the problem was,
an intern dating an attending,
until today.
Fair hours, fair wages!
And don't believe 2519 when she tells
you that she went to the bathroom.
She says she went to the bathroom
and then she's back here two days later.
- Got it.
- I need sutures in 2602.
Can't help you.
What?
Fair hours, fair wages!
Fair hours, fair...
- It's no offense.
- None taken.
Hey, how's the strike going?
Do you know...
do you realize how rarely
doctors say thank you
and please to nurses?
How few surgeons
even know the names of the...?
I shouldn't be seen talking to you.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Richard Webber?
Can I help you?
My name is Alice Bickham.
I'm here about my mother, Grace.
Sure. Um... come with me, please.
Any available nurse to admitting.
- You said you would look after her.
- I'm sorry?
You told me to go to work
and you said you would look after her.
Ms. Woods, um, can you...
just follow me?
Nurses' station.
She's a kid, you know.
She's scared enough without you
putting ideas in her head.
How do you tell a scared kid
to give her baby away?
I didn't tell her. I didn't advise her.
I didn't pressure her.
I just... talked to her.
You're not a shrink.
You're not her mother.
She's my kid. And you crossed the line.
- I'm sorry.
- You're not. You're superior.
So what, you're a big shot doctor
and you get to judge us?
You get to tell my kid
how to live her life?
Cheyenne is smart.
She's smart and she's thoughtful
and she can have more.
She can have more
than a trailer park
and a graveyard shift at a truck stop
diner. Don't you want that for her?
I mean, if you can... get past
the fact that I'm superior
and that I'm judging you and that I'm
telling you what's best for your family.
If you could just get past
all of that,
isn't it possible
that I'm also right?
Pretty spectacular recovery, Claire.
Really? Do you think
it's going to be OK?
We got almost all of
the necrotic tissue.
A few times in a hyperbaric chamber
and you'll be out of the woods.
Thank you for saving my leg.
My pleasure.
Dr. Karev will explain
the hyperbaric chamber. Dr. Karev?
Thank you, Dr. Heron.
- A hyperbaric chamber...
- I'll take that apology any time.
Thank you.
So I'm going to give her a sedative,
which will ease her discomfort.
And then I'll remove the tube. OK.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Wait.
Goodbye, Mommy.
Oh. Do you want to...?
Oh, no. No, we've already
said our good-byes.
We just wanted to be here
when Grace crossed over.
Ready.
- I can take care of this.
- I did it. I should undo it.
How long? I mean, before...?
It can take a while.
- She wants me to apologize.
- You crossed the line.
- You made me cross the line.
- Oh, like I can make you do anything.
It's not your fault.
It's mine.
I'm your teacher.
I'm supposed to be.
But you came to me as your boyfriend.
And I responded that way.
- I'm not used to being wrong.
- I know. But you're an intern.
Second-guessing a resident
is not your job.
How long has it been?
Two hours and 17 minutes.
I saw you there.
At the nursing home
with my mother.
Oh.
They said you go
two or three times a week.
Whenever I can.
Why did you keep it a secret?
I don't know.
Would you like me to stop going?
I'm going to go check on Grace.
Do you think she's Ionely?
My mother?
Yeah, I do.
May she rest in peace.
Time of death...
12:42.
I don't... I can't,
I can't, I don't...
I don't... I can't.
I don't want...
I don't want my mother to die alone.
Slow down.
Just slow down.
Shh.
Slow deep breaths now.
Slow deep breaths.
Slow down. Slow down.
Just breathe in the bag.
I'm OK.
You're OK.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Do you ever wish
you hadn't done it?
No. I really don't.
If I give her up...
if I give her away,
do I still get to name her?
You can name her for yourself.
Did you name yours?
Sarah.
That's a pretty name.
Yeah.
I think you should keep visiting her.
You sure?
Yeah.
She lights up when you're around.
She's alive.
Oh, she's with Alex.
I can't do this in front of Alex.
- Well, you can and you will.
- Excuse me, why aren't you apologizing?
I'm an attending,
I don't apologize to residents.
You, on the other hand,
are an intern.
Any available scrub nurse to OR 3.
Sydney, I just wanted to...
...uh, just wanted to, um...
...apologize for, you know,
overstepping... I'm sorry.
Well, that's the compassion
I was looking for.
Apology accepted.
OK, you want to hug it out?
- Oh.
- Go. Hug.
- Oh. Yeah.
- Come on.
Nurses at Seattle Grace are...
- We need them, Patricia.
- Yes, we need them.
So where do I find
the spare change?
It's not like what's hiding underneath
the couch cushions is going to do it.
I seem to remember pushing paperwork for
a multi-million dollar surgery robot.
There was a waiting list for that.
It will bring in huge business.
And could you and the robot handle
that business without nurses?
We can't help ourselves.
We see a line,
we want to cross it.
Maybe it's the thrill of trading
the familiar for the unfamiliar.
- A sort of personal dare.
- Congratulations.
Only problem is...
once you've crossed
it's almost impossible to go back.
You OK?
Yeah. You know, I am.
Yeah.
What happened today?
- Nothing.
OK.
We don't know everything
about each other, George.
Yeah.
True.
But, if you do manage
to make it back across that line,
you find safety in numbers.
- Anybody want to have sex?
- George.
www.tvsubtitles.net